HUSTxTJU
每当我想起我的妻子时
When I think of my wife...
我总是想起她的头
...I always think of her head.
我想象着敲碎她可爱的头盖骨
I picture cracking her lovely skull...
窥探她的大脑...
Unspooling her brains...
试图找到答案
Trying to get answers.
任何婚姻的主要问题
The primal questions of any marriage.
“你在想什么？”
"What are you thinking?"
“你在感受着什么？”
"How are you feeling?"
“我们对彼此做了什么？”
"What have we done to each other?"
消失的爱人
爱尔兰王子大驾光临啊
The Irish prince graces us with his presence.
王子殿下可不想被溅湿
His majesty prefers not to be moistened.
我给你买了个礼物
I got you a present.
我讨厌这个游戏-你喜欢它的
-I hated this game.-You loved it.
是你喜欢它
You loved it.
谢谢 我会收藏好它的
Thank you.I'll add it to the collection.
能给我倒杯波本吗
Can you pour me a bourbon?
怎么了，神经过敏症患者
What's up, jitters?
如果你再不说，我就另外讲个闷死人的
Well, if you're not going to talk,I'm gonna have to fill the silence...
玛格.道恩的故事来打破沉默了
With another excruciating storyby margo dunne.
我可以给你讲讲最近的顾客服务经历
I could tell you about my recent customer service experience...
-不讲网络供应商了 -我喜欢那个故事
-Changing Internet service providers. -I like that one.
或者讲讲我看见的那个像和
Or how about the time I saw that woman
我朋友莫妮卡从一个坯子里造出来的女人？
who looked exactly like my friend Monica?
但她不是莫妮卡，完全是一个素不相识的人
But it wasn't Monica.I t was a total stranger.
碰巧也叫莫妮卡吗
Who was also named Monica.
-听起来挺有趣 -很不错
-Made it kind of interesting. -It's great.
我今天过得很糟糕
I'm just having a bad day.
-艾米？ -是结婚纪念日
-Amy? -It's our anniversary.
-五周年 -五年了？
-Five years. -Five?
岁月飞逝啊
That came fast.
并且充满喧嚣
and furious
我真是疯狂、愚蠢的快乐
I'm so crazy, stupid happy.
我遇到一个男孩
I met a boy.
一个酷到没朋友的贴心的家伙
A great, sweet, gorgeous, cool-ass guy.
打扰一下，小姐
Excuse me, miss?
我只是想提醒你
I just want you to be careful...
不要乱放你的比利时私酿纯麦啤酒
Where you put down that monk-brewed Belgian wheat beer...
因为派对只剩下三瓶野兽青啤和一瓶帕克威士忌了
Because the party's down to three beast lights and a bottle of pucker.
那可能会逼他们狗急跳墙
It might attract some desperate characters.
也许吧 我想说那些阿米什人真是大开斋戒啊
It could. I mean, the amish are on a rumspringa.
他们已经把我从肉盘中解放了
They already relieved me of my artisanal meat platter.
终于有人教会我那个词的发音了
Finally, someone tells me how to pronounce that word.
”肉“
"meat"?
是的，“肉”，一个音节
Yes, "meat." One syllable.
谢谢你 话说我这喝的是谁的酒啊
Thank you. Whose beer am I about to drink?
别告诉我
Don't tell me.
让我来猜猜你喜欢的类型
Let's see, who's your type?
我没瞧见你安安静静地坐着听
I don't see you sitting quietly...
那人对自己的普鲁斯特硕士论文的高谈阔论
While he bloviates on his postgrad thesis about proust.
普鲁斯特：法国二十世纪最伟大的文学家 意识流代表作家 ,著作《追忆逝水年华》与《尤利西斯》合为西方现代文学双壁
是他吗？
Uh-oh. Is that him?
毒舌嬉皮士，自我意识强烈，游戏人生
Ironic hipster, so self-aware, he makes everything a joke.
我更喜欢有趣的男人，而不是滑稽的男人
I prefer men who are funny, not "funny."
你是什么类型的
What type are you?
心地单纯的密苏里小镇型
Corn-fed, salt-of-the-earth Missouri guy.
密苏里的？
Missouri?
真可爱
Cute.
纽约本地人？
Native new yorker?
我的世界在哈德逊河结束
The world ends at the Hudson.
你叫什么
What's your name?
艾米
Amy.
艾米 你是谁
Well, Amy, who are you?
A、我是一个获奖贝雕人
A, I'm an award-winning scrimshander.
B、我是影响力有限的军阀
B, I'm a moderately influential warlord.
C、我为杂志撰写性格测试
C, I write personality quizzes for magazines.
好吧 你的纤纤细手完全不适合雕刻
Okay. Your hands are far too delicate for real scrimshaw work...
我碰巧又订了小军阀生存周刊
And I happen to be a charter subscriber to middling warlord weekly...
所以我能认出你的
So I'd recognize you.
我选C
I'm gonna go with "c."
那你呢
And you?
你是干嘛的
Who are you?
我是把你从这一团乌烟瘴气中拯救出来的人
I'm the guy to save you from all this awesomeness.
所以你是给男性杂志写文章的
So, you write for a men's magazine.
我的天，这让你成为了一个怎么当男人的专家么？
God, does that make you an expert on being a man?
不
No.
你懂的，就是写写穿点什么时髦，喝点什么爷们
t's what to wear, what to drink.
怎么胡说八道
How to bullshit.
永不对你胡扯
Never with you.
蛤 蛤
Ha, ha.
没有 我是说真的
No, I mean it.
你觉得我会相信吗
It's hard to believe you.
为什么
Why?
我想是因为你的下巴
I think it's your chin.
我下巴？
My chin?
对，看起来坏坏的
Yeah, it's quite villainous.
好吧，那这样呢
Okay, how's this?
百分百真诚，绝不胡扯
A hundred percent true, no bullshit.
行啊
Okay.
我们都搬到纽约
We all move to New York...
结果住进这些逼仄的耗子洞，这还没完
And we end up living in these little cubby holes, and that's not it.
一出来，你就身在其中了
Come outside. Then, you're in it.
你必须得瞧瞧这个
You have to see this.
你好
Hey.
我必须吻你了
I have to kiss you now.
这样好吗？
Is that right?
我不能让你从头甜到脚却不吻你
I can't let you go through a sugar storm unkissed.
等一等
Wait a second.
好了
There you go.
所以，艾米是要弄个寻宝游戏
So, is Amy gonna do one of those anniversary...
来纪念周年咯
Treasure hunts?
你是说专门设计来证明
You mean the forced march designed to prove...
她有一个健忘不称职丈夫的强制性游戏？
What an oblivious and uncaring asshole her husband is?
生活 我不知道还有什么意思
Life. I don't remember the point.
思想挺深刻啊
Deep hasbro thoughts.
转
Spin.
去年令她感到极其愤怒的线索是啥？
What was the clue last year she got so mad about?
“当你可怜的艾米一得小感冒
"When your poor Amy has a cold...
这些甜品就得全卖掉”
This dessert just must be sold."
答案是？
The answer?
我至今不知道答案，继续
I still don't know the answer, go.
-几年前你肯定知道 -几年前，这游戏还很有趣
-A few years ago, you'd have known. -A few years ago, it was fun.
头一年，是纸婚
Year one, the traditional gift was paper.
她送给我漂亮的笔记本让我写小说
She got me a beautiful notebook. Told me to go write my novel.
你送给她什么？
What did you get her?
风筝
A kite.
-她从不放风筝 -好吧
-She'd never flown a kite. -Okay.
总之呢，到了第四年，花婚
Anyway. Year four, flowers.
她把我领到后院枯萎的玫瑰丛旁
She led me outside to the dying rosebush in the backyard.
有点象征意义
That's symbolic.
嗯
Yeah.
那第五年是什么婚呢？
What's the gift for five?
木婚
Wood.
-那么你给她什么礼物呢 -木头能有什么礼物呢
-So, what did you get her? -There's no good gift for wood.
我懂了 回去操晕她，用你的大屌抽死她
I know! Go home, fuck her brains out, slap her with your penis.
然后问：“这算木头礼物吗，贱人。”
"There's some wood for you, bitch."
这里是酒吧
The bar.
嗯，在 等一下
Why, yes. Hang on one second.
嘿，是管家婆瓦利
Hey, it's watchful Wally.
嘿，沃尔特，怎么了？
Hey, Walt. What's going on?
十分感谢 我马上回去
Thanks very much. I'll be right there.
好的，再见
All right, bye-bye.
嘿，老弟，跑外面来干什么
Hey, buddy. What are you doing out here?
谢谢了，沃尔特
Thanks, Walt!
艾米？
Ame?
艾米！
Amy!
有人吗
Hello?
进来吧
Come on in.
你好
Hey.
-道恩先生 -你好
-Mister dunne. -Hi.
我是朗达邦尼探员，这是吉尔平警员
I'm detective Rhonda boney.This is officer James gilpin.
我们理解你对你妻子的担心
We understand there are concerns about your wife.
我不知道我妻子在哪儿，回来就看见这个
I don't know where my wife is. And I came home to this.
我不太容易恐慌
Now, I don't panic easily...
但这太诡异了
But it's weird, right?
介意我四处看看吗？
Mind if we look around?
请便
Please.
你们在这里住了多久？
How long have you two been here?
到九月就两年了 我们之前住在纽约
Two years in September. We used to live in New York.
纽约城？
City?
嗯 我是个作家 我们都是
Yeah, I was a writer. We were both writers.
你们为什么要搬回这里？
Why did you all move back here?
我妈妈生病了
My mom got sick.
很抱歉 她还好吗
Oh, I'm sorry. How is she?
她去世了
She's dead.
非常抱歉
I'm so sorry.
你现在做什么工作？
What do you do now, for work?
我姐姐玛格和我在市中心开了家酒吧
My sister margo and I own the bar downtown.
噢，“酒吧”啊
Oh, the bar.
名字大赞 简洁明了
Love the name. Very meta.
谢谢
Thanks.
很漂亮
Pretty things.
待在里面
Stay.
这是我的办公室
My office, here.
裙子很漂亮
Beautiful dress.
约会之夜？
Date night?
是结婚周年纪念日
It's our anniversary.
那边是客房
It's a guest bedroom, there.
尽头是小猫的房间
Cat's room on the end.
这边我都检查过了
I checked up here.
这是厨房
This is the kitchen...
不用多说了
Obviously.
这是我妻子的办公室
This is my wife's office.
艾米的办公室
Amy's office.
山口山，真是出色的女孩
Wow. Impressive gal.
是的 我应该担心吗
Yeah. Should I be concerned?
我记得这些书
I remember these.
我很喜欢这些书
I loved these books.
等等
Wait a minute.
你妻子是超凡艾米？
Your wife is amazing Amy?
对啊，是她
Yeah. She is.
山口山
Wow.
他妈的超凡艾米要他妈的结婚了
Amazing-fucking-Amy is getting fucking married.
那一晚就是这么开始的
That's how the night started.
我，平凡、有缺点的、真实的艾米一直嫉妒那个完美的金童
With me, regular, flawed, real Amy,jealous, as always, of the golden child.
那个完美、聪明、超凡的艾米他妈的结婚了
Perfect, brilliant, amazing Amy, who's getting fucking married.
我十岁时放弃了大提琴
When I was 10, I quit cello.
下一本书中，艾米成为了一个大提琴天才
In the next book,amazing Amy became a prodigy.
你打排球吗？
Did you play volleyball?
我大一就被刷下来了
I got cut, freshman year.
她进了大学校队
She made varsity.
你什么时候养过狗狗
When did you have a dog?
是“她”养了只狗
got the dog.
狗狗让她更体贴
Puddles made her more relatable.
我喜欢你的父母
I love your parents...
但他们有时候真的很混账
But they really can be assholes.
-尼克 -先生
-Nick! -Sir!
谢谢你的光临
Hey, thanks for coming, man.
应该的
No problem.
你好，宝贝
Hey, sweetheart.
今晚对你妈妈很重要
Big night for your mom.
你最好能去给那几个记者
It would mean so much if you would talk to a few reporters...
博主谈谈天，放点小艾米的料
Bloggers, give them a little Amy color.
大家都想听听你的声音
People wanna hear from you.
-我们不会待很久的 -好极了
-We can't stay long. -Fantastic.
最多十五分钟
Fifteen minutes, tops.
这就是我有自己的公寓的原因，这是我的信托，我知道我没什么抱怨的
This is why I have my brownstone.My trust fund. I know I can't complain.
你的父母简直就是剽窃了你的童年
Your parents literally plagiarized your childhood.
不，他们“升华”了它，然后把它卖给了大众
No, they improved upon it,and then peddled it to the masses.
我本以为你的穿着会以白色为主调来彰显婚礼的主题
I thought you were gonna wear white to match the wedding theme.
我觉得那样会很奇怪
I thought that would be creepy.
“如果它值得去做，它就值得 ..."
"If it's worth doing, it's worth doing--"
等等，我知道这话怎么结束 别告诉我
"Hold on! I know how this ends. Don't tell me
你真可爱 尼克
"You're very cute, Nick.
艾米，你知道怎样让爸爸开心
"Amy, you know what would make dad's night.
我就去
"I'm on it.
我喜欢被陌生人揭伤疤
I love having strangers pick at my scabs.
我很好奇对您来说
"I'm curious whether...
眼看超凡的艾米即将步入婚姻殿堂是否很难受
"It's difficult for you to see amazing Amy heading down the aisle.
为了庆祝这个虚构的婚礼，还特意摆了盛大的排场
And this big party celebrating this fictional wedding.
因为按我的理解，你并没结婚
Because it's my understanding you are not married.
是真的吗
Is that correct?
是真的 超凡艾米总是比我抢先一步
Correct. Amazing Amy has always been one step ahead of me.
打扰一下 抱歉  我有几个问题
Excuse me. I'm sorry, I just have a few questions.
是你
It's you.
我是本着记者的专业态度来问你的
I'm here in a strictly journalistic capacity.
现在为止 你和尼克.道恩愉快地交往多久了
Now, you had the distinct pleasure of dating Nick dunne for how long?
奇妙的两年了
Two magical years.
奇妙的两年啊
在那段期间，你有很多次出于体贴
In the course of that time, you've had the opportunity...
纵容尼克傻乎乎的错误
To perform such gracious gestures as...
当他把“藜麦”念成了“梨~麦”
Not correcting Nick when he pronounced "quinoa" as "kween-o-a."
一个可以理解的错误
An understandable mistake.
他一直以为那是一种鱼
He also thought it was a fish.
velveeta：一种奶油通心粉和奶酪食谱
他还认为velveeta是奶酪
He thinks velveeta is a cheese.
每次尼克年迈的母亲见到你
You also manage to appear shocked and delighted...
都会即兴表演《纽约纽约》
When Nick's elderly mother breaks into an impromptu rendition...
而你总是流露出惊讶和欣喜之情
Of New York, New York, every time she sees you.
【歌词】These bag of bone shoes
别吓人了
that's just frightening.
你也给尼克买了他人生第一把剪刀
You also bought Nick his very first pair of scissors.
还有订书机
And matching stapler.
艾米.艾略特，你不仅是了不起的
Amy elliott, you are more than amazing.
你还才华横溢而无趋利之心
You are brilliant, yet entirely un-snobby.
你考验了我，令我惊叹
You challenge me. You surprise me.
还给读者爆点笑料
And, fun fact for the readers...
你的床上功夫世界一流
You have a world-class vagina.
我同事告诉我你还没有结婚
My colleagues tell me that you are not yet married.
是真的吗？
Is that correct?
我们是不是该填补这个遗憾了
Isn't it time we fixed that?
之后...
And then...
那一晚就不再是那么糟了
The night wasn't so bad anymore.
搞定了 这事完成了
And it's done. Crossed off the list.
言归正传，通常我们不会如此快地把这视为失踪案件
Now, normally, we would not treat this as a missing persons case so quick...
但是鉴于你家里的情况
But given the scene at your house...
以及我们在最近的暴力案件中承受的巨大压力
And given our spike in violent crime of late...
我们会非常、非常严肃地对待此案
We are gonna take this very, very seriously.
好的 很好
Okay. Good.
我们派了鉴定科的人去你家调查 你有住处吗
We've got forensics over at your place. You got somewhere to stay?
-我可以住在我姐姐那里 -好的
-I could stay at my sister's. -Okay.
我们会追踪艾米的电话 信用卡
We're tracking Amy's phone, her credit cards.
我们会组织搜查 张贴启事
We will organize searches, put up flyers.
我们明天会组织一个新闻发布会
-We're gonna hold a press conference tomorrow.
你们要开新闻发布会？
You're having a press conference?
我得套点话出来 对吧
I wanna get the word out, right?
是啊，我只是突然觉得
Yeah, it's just all of a sudden
我好像在上演《法律与秩序》
I feel like I'm on a law & order episode
时间在此类案件中至关宝贵
Time is of the essence in these cases.
但话说回来 你要等一等去找个律师吗
But, that said, do you wanna wait and call a lawyer?
当然不是 我只是想寻求帮助
Absolutely not. I just wanna help.
所以 你和艾米在这儿居住两年了
So, you and Amy have been here two years.
-你经营酒吧 -我是老板
-You tend bar -I own the bar.
我还在莫霍克谷社区学院教写作
And I teach creative writing at mvcc.
-没孩子吗？ -还没呢
-No kids? -Not yet.
那么艾米平时主要做些什么
So, what does Amy do most days?
这么高学历的一个女人，她干些什么？
A woman with all those degrees, what does she do?
我也不知道 她总是很忙
I don't know. She keeps busy.
做什么？
Doing what?
她是一个饥渴的读者
She's a voracious reader.
所以 她手里总是捧着一本书
So, she's always got a book in her hand.
但是常日慢慢
Well, days can get long.
我认识一些家庭主妇，从中午一直喝到晚上
I know a few housewives, that evening glass of wine starts coming at noon.
或者吞服处方药
Or prescription pills.
就在上周 我们有位全职顾家的母亲
Just last week, we had a soccer mom.
善良的女士,因为错吃奥施康定丢了好几颗牙齿
Nice lady. Got her teeth kicked in over some oxycontin.
自从那商场倒闭后，城里一半的人都失去了工作
Ever since that mall went bust, half the town is out of work.
我们也开始控制不了毒品暴力了
We cannot keep up with the drug violence.
我肯定那不是毒品和暴力的问题
I'm pretty sure that's not it.
艾米有什么朋友吗？
Has Amy got friends we can talk to?
没 没有
No, not really.
没有朋友？整个镇子？
No friends? This whole town?
她和我妈妈很亲密，在她去世之前
She was very close with my mom, before she passed away.
我们小区附近的流浪汉
You know, we have a pretty serious homeless problem...
很成问题
In our neighborhood.
我觉得你应该查查这个
I think maybe you guys should check that out.
我们会调查的
We'll look into that.
你是11点左右到达“酒吧”的是吧
You got to the bar around 11:00 today.
那你之前在哪？只是确认一下
Where were you before that? Just to cross that out.
我在家里
Well, I was home.
我在九点半出去的，买了杯咖啡和一份报纸
I left at 9:30, I got a cup of coffee, a newspaper.
然后去索耶沙滩看了会儿新闻
I went to Sawyer beach and read the news.
你在那碰到谁了吗？
Did you visit with anyone there?
我去那里就图享受安静好吗
I kind of go to Sawyer beach for the solitude.
所以，你的妻子在这没有朋友
So, your wife has no friends here.
她很冷淡吗？
Is she kinda standoffish?
常春藤？拒人以千里之外？
Ivy league? Rubs people the wrong way?
她是纽约人
She's from New York.
性格复杂，生活标准高
She's complicated. She's got very high standards.
A型血？
Type a?
如果你不喜欢这样你会疯的
That can make you crazy if you're not like that.
你看起来很懒散，B型血吧
You seem pretty laid-back. Type b.
说到这个，艾米什么血型？
Speaking of which, Amy's blood type?
我的天 我不知道 我得回去查一查
God, I don't know. I'd have to look it up at the house.
你不知道她有没有朋友，你不知道她一天干些什么
You don't know if she has friends, you don't know what she does all day...
你还不知道她的血型
And you don't know your wife's blood type.
你确定你已婚？
Sure you all are married?
也许是O型吧
Maybe it's type o.
-她家人在哪？纽约？ - 是的
-Where are her folks? New York? -Yeah.
能让他们出席明天的新闻发布会吗？
Can they get here time for this press conference tomorrow?
明天？ 我不知道 还没给他们说这事
Tomorrow? I have no idea. I haven't talked to them.
你还没和你妻子的父母打电话？
You haven't called your wife's parents yet?
这房间里又没信号，我又一直在和你们讲话
You can't get a signal in this building. I've been in here talking to you.
快给他们打吧，尼克，就现在
Call them, please, Nick. Now.
好吧
Fine.
我需要知道我妻子的血型吗
Should I know my wife's blood type?
不需要
No.
抱歉 玛丽贝丝 我也不知道发生了什么
I apologize, marybeth. I didn't know what was going on.
我现在在警局
Now I'm at the station...
警察在我们房子里检查，事态很严重所以我打电话给你
And the cops are at the house, and it's serious and I'm calling you.
现在很多事情还没弄清楚
There's a lot of things that are being juggled right now.
我就站在警探朗达邦尼旁边
I'm standing right next to detective Rhonda boney...
她负责这个案件
Who's the lead investigator on this and she's...
我岳母想和你说几句
My mother-in-law would like to speak with you.
我是邦尼探员
This is detective boney.
我想回家
I wanna go home.
我不明白我为何必须待在这里
I don't know why I have to be here.
我不想待在这里 我要回家
I don't wanna be here. I wanna go home.
爸爸？
Dad?
这是我父亲 发生什么了？
This is my father. What's going on?
是吗？你就是尼克道恩？
Really? You're Nick dunne?
我们一下午都在努力联系你
We've been trying to get a hold of you all afternoon.
我一直在这里 我妻子失踪了
I've been right there. My wife is missing.
-贱货 -别说了
-Bitch -Don't.
你父亲午饭后就离开养老院四处游荡
Your father wandered out of comfort hill after lunch.
我们在79路发现了他 他迷路了
We found him walking route 79, disoriented.
我们一直在给你打电话...
We've been trying to call you for the last--
我手机在这栋楼里收不到信号
I don't get a cell signal in this building.
我一直坐在离你二十英尺的地方
I've been sitting 20 feet away from you.
先生 请别用那种语调和我讲话好吗
Sir, please don't take that tone with me.
又笨又蠢又丑的贱人
Stupid, dumb, ugly bitch.
爸爸，别说了
Dad, stop.
你想要把他送回家吗？
You wanna drive him home?
我觉得那样做更明智 谢谢
I think that would be wise. Thanks.
语音邮箱已满
This voice mailbox is currently full.
操
Fuck.
把你的脏手拿开
Get your fucking hands off me.
谢谢
Thanks.
所有人都告诉我们...
Everyone told us and told us and told us...
婚姻是个苦差事
Marriage is hard work.
需要妥协和苦痛去经营
And compromise and more work.
”进入炼狱之人 勿抱尘世之望“【神曲】
"Abandon all hope, ye who enter."
“当小艾米的希望日渐消逝...
"When young Amy's hope did wane...
”她在此处游荡..."
"She wandered here..."
好吧，这不是真的，至少对我和尼克是这样
Well, it's not true.Not for me and Nick.
"...寻找简.奥斯汀“
"...in search of Jane."
对我们来说，两年...
With us, two years...
正好
It's just good.
奥斯汀
Austen.
你是一个形单影只的姑娘
You were an alienated teen
只有伊丽莎白.贝内特理解你
and only Elizabeth Bennet understood you.
看这个
Look at that.
老天爷
My God.
你这风骚的妮子
You naughty minx.
好了，按道理我们应该在下一站来一炮
Well, technically, we are supposed to fuck at the next stop.
没错 保持传统
Yeah, in keeping with tradition.
不过我想我们这次可以违反一下规则
But I might be willing to bend the rules this once.
老天保佑简.奥斯汀
God bless Jane Austen.
我很热情的 看这个 以此为证
I'm enthusiastic. Look at that. It's confirmed by the...
谢谢
Thank you.
两周年 棉婚
Year two. Cotton.
我们开过玩笑说过我们的性生活太棒了
We had that joke that our sex was too good for ordinary.
所以，我们的床单也要是2000纱支的
So, these are 2,000 thread-count--
我们两个真是太可爱了，我真想在我们脸上打一拳
we're so cute. I wanna punch us in the face.
那太好了 简直太棒了
That's pretty great. I mean, that is pretty great.
他们有问你想不想请律师吗？
Did they ask if you wanted a lawyer?
我不需要律师 这里我来吧
I don't need a lawyer. Here, I'll do this.
那他们有问艾米的私人信息吗？
Well, did they ask personal stuff about Amy?
他们问了些...
You know, they asked...
为什么她没几个朋友
Why didn't she have any friends?
你怎么说
What did you say?
-我说她很复杂 -尼克！
-I said she was complicated. -Nick!
谁都知道 复杂的意思就是贱货
Everyone knows "complicated" is code for "bitch."
天哪 我觉得很难受
God. I feel sick.
谢了
Thanks.
这事太奇怪了
It's so bizarre.
感觉它注定会发生在艾米身上似的
It seems like the kind of thing that would happen to Amy.
她总是吸引--
She always attracts--
戏剧性？
drama?
你可以说出来 只有我俩
You can say it. It's just me and you.
只是因为我不想待在艾米身边
Just because I don't like to be around Amy...
并不代表我不关心她
Doesn't mean I don't care about her.
总之 带走她的人肯定会带她回来的
Anyway, whoever took her is bound to bring her back.
警探吗？你好
Detective? Excuse me.
我是诺艾尔.霍桑 艾米最好的朋友
I'm noelle hawthorne. I'm Amy's best friend.
那太好了，你住在哪？诺艾尔
Well, great. Where do you live, noelle?
隔着五家人 1032号
Five doors down. 1032.
非常好，我很愿意与你谈一谈
Wonderful. I would love to talk to you.
我能半个小时后过去吗？
Can I come by in half an hour?
有什么消息了吗？
-Y'all know anything yet? -I'm sorry.
我现在要找个人，等我30分钟好吗
I got guys on the clock in here.But you give me 30 minutes.
但那一般是我的洗漱时间
But that's usually bath time.
那就边洗边说吧
Well, we'll talk in between shampoos.
好了，那么，你发现了什么？
All right. So, what do you got?
你在厨房看见的肯定是飞溅的血滴
It was definitely blood spatter you saw in the kitchen.
通常这不奇怪，厨房，刀具，准备食物
Normally, kitchen, knives, food prep.
但那血迹太高了
Not that weird, but that is awfully high.
所以，我叫人用发光氨检测血迹
So, I'm gonna order a luminol sweep.
好的
Well, okay.
有意思
Interesting.
什么？
What's that?
房子是以她的名义出租的 车主也是她
House is rented in her name. Car's in her name.
信用卡、家用设施、电话账单都在她名下
Credit cards, utilities, phone bill, all in her name.
连他的酒吧都在她名下
Even his bar's in her name.
我不觉得这有什么惊讶的
I don't know that that's so surprising.
不奇怪 但很丢脸
No. But it is humiliating.
你发现了什么？
What you got?
在她的私密储存室发现的
It's with her unmentionables.
好了，我们找到了第一条线索
Well, we have our first clue.
我得冲个澡
I have to take a shower.
不 不要 你一晚上都没睡好
No, don't. You've been up all night.
你得看着像一夜没睡的样子
You wanna look like you've been up all night.
今天当心点 好吗？
Hey, be careful today, okay?
说得还真奇怪
That's a weird thing to say.
当你沮丧时 你会酗酒 你会变得很愤怒 就像--
Well, when you're upset, you bottle up. You can seem angry, like--
请别说跟爸爸一个德行
please don't say, "like dad."
要不然就摇身变为人见人疼的乖宝宝，防御爆表，那就耍滑头咯
Or else you swing into your momma's- boy charm offensive and that can feel glib
完美
Perfect.
我会照顾好你柔弱易碎的内心的
I'll balance on the exact fucking edge of your emotional razor.
好吧 你只需要
Okay. Just be...
做我自己？
Myself?
...赞助了一个彩票抽奖店来造福西部人民
...sponsoring a raffle to benefit west county 4h...
出售密苏里足球队的赛季票
And raffling season tickets for mizzou football.
你可以在当地烤翅店买或轮胎店买到球票
Buy your tickets at the wing hut or local tri-state tire stores.
你岳父已经到了
Your in-laws made it.
-嗨 兰德 -你好 孩子
-Hi, rand. -Hey, man.
我是邦尼探员
I'm detective boney.
我是她的孪生姐姐 玛格
I'm the twin. Margo.
我们昨天打了排球 尼克 我现在还没缓过来
We played tennis yesterday, Nick. I just can't get over it.
我很抱歉 玛丽贝丝
Marybeth, I am really sorry.
我就知道你们真不该搬回来
I knew you never should have moved back here.
我们没有什么选择余地
We didn't have a lot of choice.
我们都很担心 我们都很害怕
We are all worried. We are all scared.
但我们都聚在这里了 我们一定会共同找到艾米
But we are all here now. And we will find Amy, together.
是我先来 然后你们再说点什么吗
Should I just go first, and then you guys can say something?
很好
Good.
如你们所知 我妻子 艾米.艾略特.道恩
As you know, my wife, Amy elliott dunne...
七月五日在我们家失踪了
Disappeared from our home on the morning of July 5th...
留下许多可疑的线索
Under suspicious circumstances.
大声点
Louder!
如果诸位有任何消息
If anyone out there has any information...
请站出来
Please come forward.
谢谢
Thank you.
我是兰德.艾略特 这是我妻子 玛丽贝丝.艾略特
I'm rand elliott. My wife, marybeth elliott.
我应该说我名字吗？
Should I have said my name?
艾米是我们唯一的孩子
Amy is our only child.
她阳光 美丽 心底善良
She's bright, she's beautiful.   She's kind.
她的确是超凡的艾米
She really is amazing Amy.
有千千万万的人
You know, there are millions of people out there...
同她一起成长 并关心着她
who grew up with her,and care about her.
我们关心着她 我们深爱她
We care about her, we love her.
我们只想她魅影重现
And we just want her back.
艾米是一位杰出的学者
Amy is a decorated scholar.
在新闻业铸就了一段非凡的事业
She forged a successful career in journalism.
她回到这儿 他丈夫的家乡
She returned here to her husband's hometown...
在婆家开始了新的生活
And she made a life in her adopted home.
现在 艾米需要你们的援助
Now, Amy needs your help.
我们在德鲁里旅馆设立了志愿者中心
We're establishing a volunteer headquarters at the drury lodge.
我们的热线电话是1-855-4-寻找艾米
We have a hotline, 1-855-4-Amy-tips.
我们的网站是www.Findamazingamy.Com
And our website is www.Findamazingamy.Com.
-道恩先生! -艾略特先生！
-Mr. Dunne! -Mr.Elliott!
道恩先生 有没有任何凶杀的迹象
Mr. dunne, any signs of foul play?
艾略特先生 你上一次和你女儿说话是什么时候
Mr. elliott, when was the last time you spoke to your daughter?
笑
Smile.
艾米是那种吸引很多爱慕者的女孩
Amy is the kind of girl who attracts admirers.
对吧 尼克？
Right, Nick?
是的 的确是
Yeah, definitely.
我们知道几个例子
And we've had instances...
-这些例子有点--  吓人
Where things got-- -scary.
你知道德西.柯林斯吗？
Do you know about desi collings?
是的 我知道德西.柯林斯的事
Yeah, I know all about desi collings.
他对艾米极其痴迷
He was obsessed.
艾米在高二和他分手后他曾试图自杀
He attempted suicide after Amy broke up with him sophomore year.
我们不得不申请了一份禁令
We had to file a restraining order.
这发生在中学的时候 二十年前？
This would be high school? Twenty years ago?
但他最近搬到了圣路易斯 离这里只要两小时车程
But he recently moved to St. Louis. That's just two hours away.
其实 他老家就是圣路易斯的
To be fair, he is from St. Louis.
还有汤米.奥哈拉
We also have Tommy O'Hara.
这只发生在八年前 在纽约
This is only eight years ago, in New York.
他和她分手后 他变得很暴力
She broke up with him, he got very physical.
-她提出了诉讼 -罪名是什么？
-She filed charges. -What was the charge?
性侵 威胁 恐吓 还是什么？
Sexual assault, threat, battery, what?
我只知道情况很糟糕
I only know it was bad.
-我竟然不知道这事 -好吧
-I didn't know this. -Okay.
谢谢你们
Thank you
还有什么最近的事吗
Anything more recently?
我不知道别的什么了
Not that I know of.
尼克 能借几分钟吗
Hey, Nick? You got a minute?
当然
Yeah.
想一想我们的困惑
Imagine our confusion.
一个人员失踪案件
A missing persons case...
而我们却在你妻子的更衣室里找到一个写着“线索”的信封
And in your wife's dressing room,we find an envelope marked "clue."
那是为我们的结婚纪念日准备的
That's for our anniversary.
我妻子喜欢这些寻宝游戏
My wife does these treasure hunts.
我希望你能告诉我其中有何意义
I'm hoping you can tell me what this means.
你想玩艾米设计的寻宝游戏？
You want to solve Amy's treasure hunt?
这能帮我追踪艾米消失前的行动
It'll help me track Amy's movements before she disappeared.
当然 可以
Of course. Okay.
尽管此地逼仄狭窄
"Although this spot couldn't be tighter...
却为我景仰作家之最爱
"It's a cozy room for my favorite writer."
我知道这个地方
I know this one!
尽管此地逼仄狭窄
Although this spot couldn't be any tighter...
却为我所仰慕作家之最爱
It's a cozy room for my favorite writer.
铃响后相聚 别问我心为何
After-school meeting, don't mind if I do.
好老师的心总是神秘莫测
Maybe I'll teach you a thing or two.
好了，好了，那上面写了什么
Well, well. What does it say?
线索二
Clue two.
嘿 帅哥 让我们暗中游戏吧
"Hey, handsome man, let's go undercover.
你饰演间谍 我来扮演他的情人
"You'll be the spy, and I'll be his lover.
“让我们携手并肩地前往...
"Let's head on over...
"那间棕色的小屋
"To the little brown house.
”我们扮演热辣溺爱的夫妻 甜蜜钟情的爱侣."
"We'll play hot, doting husband,  sweet, loving spouse."
这是你的吗？(/▽＼)
These yours?
不是
No.
但你读了线索一
But you read the first clue.
色色的教授，调皮的学生
Randy Professor, naughty student.
我都觉得害羞
I blush.
我和前任都只交换过名片
Me and my ex just swapped cards.
那个棕色小屋是什么？
Where's this little brown house?
我不知道
I have no idea.
你好？
Hello?
我是尼古拉斯.道恩
Nicholas dunne.
这房子在我父亲威廉.道恩名下
Under my father's name, William dunne.
我妻子的第一只宠物 这有必要吗？
My wife's first pet? Is this necessary?
你能稍微关一关警报吗
Can you just turn the bell--
是的 我明白
yeah, I know.
它是...它是...
It's... it's...
它是“泥坑”，对吗  或者是“狮子狗“
It's "puddles," right?  Or is it "poodles?"
没事了
We're good.
陌生人你好
Hello, stranger.
没想到在这遇到你
Fancy meeting you here.
这是你爸的房子，是吗？
It's your dad's house, right?
你是在跟踪我吗？
Are you following me?
你在做什么？
What you doing?
如你所说 它是我爸爸的房子
Like you said, it's my dad's house.
我每周从这里路过一次 确定这里没遭火灾
I come by once a week, make sure the place hasn't burned down.
但它看来挺不错
But it looks okay.
我送你出去吧
I'll walk you out.
你知道吗？
You know...
我想这就是那个棕色小屋
I thought maybe this was the little brown house.
线索上写的那个
From the clue.
不是 还是蓝的
Nope. Still blue.
设想我是一个很坏很坏的女孩
Picture me,I'm a girl who's very, very bad.
我需要被惩罚 被惩罚 我的意思是 活该
I need to be punished,and by "punished," I mean "had."
它就是你存放五周年纪念礼物的地方
It's where you keep goodies for anniversary five.
所以快打开门，仔细一看
"So open the door, and look alive."
贱货
Bitch!
想要测试一下你婚姻的软肋吗？
Want to test your marriage for weak spots?
加上一次经济衰退
Add one recession...
再扣去两份工作
Subtract two jobs.
这真是令人惊讶的有效
It's surprisingly effective.
向我保证我们永远也不会变成那样
Promise me we'll never be like them.
像谁？
Like who?
所有我们认识的糟糕的夫妻
All those awful couples we know.
那些妻子把丈夫当成杂耍的猴子一样
Those wives who treat their men like dancing monkeys...
训得服服帖帖然后被牵出去炫耀
To be trained and paraded.
丈夫面对妻子就像面对高速公路的巡警
Husbands who treat their wives like the highway patrol...
时刻算计着又小心提防着
To be out-foxed and avoided.
我觉得我会失业
I think I'm gonna be laid off.
我们正处于经济萧条中，如果发生了，我们能应付的
We're in a recession.If it happens, we'll deal with it.
我可能就是下一个
I'll probably be next.
我们还有彼此
We have each other.
其他一切都微不足道
Everything else is background noise.
你独一无二
You are exceptional.
我父母的出版商把他们踹了，他们现在债台高筑
My parents' publisher dropped them,and they're in debt up to their ears.
太糟糕了
That's terrible.
他们现在需要从我的信托里借钱
And they need to borrow from my trust fund.
拿了多少
How much?
差不多一百万
Almost a million.
那几乎都要花完了
That's almost all of it.
这是你说的，“其他的一切都是微不足道的“
This is where you say,"everything else is background noise."
艾米 如果你失业了
Amy, if you're laid off...
我也失业了
And I'm laid off...
我说了我会借的
I said I'd do it.
都不告知我一声吗？
Without talking to me?
-但，这 -你说了算
Well, it's...-Your call.
准确的说是他们的钱
...their money, technically.
你说得很对
You know what? You're right.
其他一切都无足轻重
Everything else is just background noise.
BF3（男朋友3）
又是游戏？
More games?
没错 我就想射死一些人
Yeah, I just wanted to shoot some folks.
这个笔记本是拿来干嘛的？
What's the laptop for
用啊
Laptop-ing.
我明白了
I see.
你可以不和我商量就借给你父母八十九万...
You can give your parents $879,000 without talking to me...
我他妈不经你允许买款电子游戏就触犯上帝了
But God forbid I buy a video game without getting your permission.
你花了很多了
You are spending a lot.
你不信任我 你不相信我的判断力
You don't trust me.You don't trust my judgment.
你甚至怀疑我的动机
You certainly don't trust my intention.
你胡说什么呢
What are you talking about?
那是婚前协议的基本条约 不是吗？
That's the basic tenet of a prenup, isn't it?
你为什么老那那个说事？
Why are you throwing that in my face again?
因为我本来就有理有据
Because it's easy to throw.
尼克，我就不懂了
Nick, I don't get it.
我不懂你为什么老是逼着我变成那种我憎恨的女人
I don't get why you're daring me to be someone I don't wanna be.
唠叨的泼妇，控制欲爆表的婊子
The nagging shrew.The controlling bitch.
我不是那样的人，我是你妻子
I'm not that person. I'm your wife.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我只不知道如何面对这一切 我以前从未失业过
I just don't know how to do this  I've never not had a job.
我卖过汉堡 刷过墙...
I flipped burgers, I painted houses.
你可以另找一个工作
You'll get another job.
嗨 格
Hi, go.
什么 等等 你说什么
What? Hold on. What?
-突然间 -慢点说 怎么了
-And suddenly... -Slow down, what is it?
我知道一切都将会越来越糟
...I knew everything was about to get worse.
告诉我发生了什么
Okay, tell me what's wrong.
-上帝保佑你 尼克 -神父
-Bless you, Nick. -Father.
你好 汤姆 镇长先生！
Hey, tom. Mayor!
很高兴见到你 尼克
Nick, good to see you.
我也是
Good to see you.
小家伙们
Hey, guys, hey.
-朱迪 -尼克
-Jodie. -Nick.
我们会找到她的
Oh, we'll find her.
你脸色真差
You look like hammered shit.
谢谢
Thank you.
你以前见过那个戴眼镜的家伙吗
You ever see that guy in the glasses before?
别担心 我们录下了从这里进出的每一个人
Don't worry. We videotape everybody that comes in and out of these things.
我是说，你真是找来了不少
I mean, you tend to get a lot of...
伪慈善家
Do-gooders?
怪胎
Freaks.
嘿，我想问问你
Hey, I meant to ask you.
认识诺艾尔霍桑吗？
Noelle hawthorne?
她住在你那条街上，是艾米最好的朋友
She lives on your street.Amy's best friend.
我从没听说过诺艾尔.霍桑
I've never heard the name Noelle Howthorne
她生了个三胞胎
She and her husband have triplets.
哦
Oh.
我们可能在街上跟他们打过几次招呼
Yeah, we might say hi to them on the street.
但“最好的朋友” 太夸张了
But "best friend"? No.
抱歉 等我一下
Excuse me, one sec.
他表现的好像诺艾尔是个完全的陌生人
He acted like noelle was a complete stranger.
瞧 这两个都归你了
Look, these two are yours.
他在扮演大好人呢
Oh, look. He's being a good guy...
这样人们才会觉得他很无辜
So everybody can see him being a good guy.
他有哪点讨人喜欢
What's to like?
语音信箱已满 请按1转到...
This mailbox is currently full. Press one to--
尼克？ 请允许我自我介绍下 我是肖娜.凯莉
Nick? I just wanted to introduce myself. My name's shawna Kelly.
我为你的困境感到十分难过
I am so sorry for your troubles.
谢谢你的关心
Thank you. That's kind.
你是难过得忘记用餐了吗
Are you remembering to eat?
我吃了不少冷切肉
Well, a lot of cold cuts.
那我得用我世界闻名的玉米鸡肉派款待你一番
I'm gonna fix you up my world-famous chicken frito pie.
感谢你的好意 不用劳烦了
That's very kind and very unnecessary.
吃好了才有力量做事嘛
You have to keep your strength.
你能...
Would you...
说 “玉米鸡肉派”
Say, "chicken frito pie!"
那个
You know what?
能麻烦你删了这张照片吗
Would you delete that picture for me?
-这张照片很可爱啊 -我知道
-It's a nice photo. -I know it is.
就算帮我个忙吧
But just do me a favor.
行吗
Will you?
求求你删了这张照片吧
Would you go ahead and please delete that picture?
你只需轻轻按下...
You just press...
你有病吧
What is wrong with you?
别把它放到社交网站上去好吗
Could you please not share that with anyone?
我爱给谁分享就给谁分享
I will share it with whomever I please.
-老爷 -怎么了
-Dude. -Yeah?
玛丽贝丝气疯了
Marybeth is pissed.
为什么
Why?
玛丽贝丝
Marybeth?
你表现得像个该死的归国国王
It's like you're the goddamn homecoming king.
我妈妈曾教导我 为人要礼貌
It was important to my mother that I be polite...
体贴 有绅士风度
I be considerate, I be a gentleman.
我只看到你玩得很嗨
It looked like you were having fun.
我身处噩梦一般
I am in a nightmare!
我只是想在那些志愿帮助寻找艾米的人面前
All I'm trying to do is be nice...
尽量表现得从容一点
To the people who are volunteering to help find Amy.
你说得对
You're right.
我很抱歉
And I'm sorry.
老天 这地方的气味真令人作呕
My God, this place literally smells like feces.
你在搜索时有看到一根高尔夫球杆吗？很高档的那种
In your searches,did you find any golf clubs, real fancy?
没有
No.
那有没有一把崭新的电吉他
How about a brand new stratocaster?
也没有那种东西
No, nothing like that.
那好吧
Well, all right.
那台电视有多大？不是65吋的吧
How big's that TV? It's not 65-inch.
不 差得远
No, it's nowhere near that.
-有猫粮吗？-什么？
-Kibble?-Excuse me?
他叫我帮他喂猫
He asked me to feed his cat.
我在食品柜里看到一些
I saw some in the pantry.
邦尼警探 吉尔平警官 我是诺艾尔.霍桑
Detective boney, officer gilpin? Noelle hawthorne!
我知道你们都在里面
I know y'all are in there!
能请你把霍恩女士和她的孩子送回街上吗？
Would you please escort miss hawthorne and her children back out to the street?
邦尼警探
Detective boney!
就告诉她这里是可能的犯罪现场
Just remind her it is a possible crime scene.
看看这惬意的微笑 竟然来自一个妻子失踪的男人
Look at that pie-eating grin, from a guy whose wife is missing.
-你还好吗 -不能更好了
-How are you doing? -Terrific.
玛丽贝丝呢
How's marybeth?
她很不开心
She's a wreck.
你呢
And you?
开心极了
Awesome.
你有什么事瞒着我吗
Have you told me everything?
当然没有
Of course.
一件都没？
Everything?
你怎么这样问我
Why would you even ask me that?
自打你在艾米失踪的那天早上走进酒吧起 你就显得
Ever since you walked into the bar that morning Amy went missing, you seem...
-心不在焉 -当然了
-Off. -I am off.
人人都在质疑我 背后对我说三道四
Everybody's examining me and projecting their shit on me.
我唯一想的就是到这儿来 和你喝杯啤酒
All I want is to come over here, have a beer with you...
不被人评论
And not be judged.
行吗
Can we do that?
当然可以
Of course.
你知道我在想什么吗
You know what I keep thinking?
如果妈妈也在这里
If mom were here?
是啊 就像我十二岁的时候
Yeah. Like I'm 12.
尼克 如果妈妈还健在 一定会处理好这一切
Nick, mom would fix it.
我要吃药睡觉了
I'm gonna go Benadryl myself to sleep.
-爱你 -爱你
-Love you. -Love you.
好了，这是一个奇怪的新句子
So, here's a strange, new sentence.
我是一个密苏里人
I am a missourian.
再见，爸
Bye, dad.
没有钱，没有工作，没有希望
No money, no jobs, no prospects.
然后，我们接到来了戈的电话
And then, we heard from go.
莫林妈妈
Mama Maureen...
乳腺癌晚期
Stage 4 breast cancer.
所以，我们搬到了密苏里
So, we moved to Missouri.
我不介意
I don't mind.
我只是希望他能问一问
I just wish he'd asked.
尼克回到家很高兴
Nick is happy to be home.
但我不知道他是否因为我陪伴他而高兴
But I don't know if he's happy I'm with him.
我感觉像是一个他背错的包袱
I feel like something he loaded by mistake.
一件注定被遗弃的东西
Something to be jettisoned,if necessary.
一件用完即弃的东西
Something disposable.
我感觉我可以从此消失
I feel like I could disappear.
我的天
Oh, my God!
-我在电视上看见你了 -好吧
-I saw you on TV. -Okay.
-这太疯狂了  -是啊 我知道
-It's so crazy. -Yeah, I know.
-她就这样消失了 -她只是离家出走了
-She just vanished? -She's just gone.
-我担心死里你 -你都去哪儿了
-I've been so worried about you. -Where have you been?
我给你打了无数次电话 你接电话呀
I called you a hundred times. You gotta pick up your phone!
我在排练
Rehearsals.
什么
What?
福音
Godspell.
我姐姐就在隔壁睡觉
My sister's asleep in the other room.
我很想见你
I needed to see you.
我觉得这样太不理智了
I know this is a bad idea.
你至少得对我说你爱我
Can you at least tell me you love me?
我真的爱你 但我们现在要非常小心
I do love you, but we have to be really careful right now.
我被吓坏了
I've been so scared.
彩排间隙？
Between rehearsals?
你告诉过我要有自己的生活
You told me I needed to have my own life.
我知道
I know.
我们得克制
We need to stop.
我需要你
I need you.
摸摸我
Touch me.
停了 过来
Stop it. Come here.
坐下
Sit down.
好的
Okay.
你有偶然告诉过任何人 关于我俩的任何事吗
Did you, by any chance, tell anybody anything about us?
发信息或在脸书上透露过也算
Even in texting, or on Facebook.
脸书？我用的是一次性手机
Facebook? I use the disposable phone.
你给我买礼物也都用现金 我不蠢 尼克
You buy my presents in cash. I'm not stupid, Nick.
我懂 甜心 你是不是在我办公室丢了条红内裤
I know, sweetie. Did you leave a pair of red panties in my office?
我不知道 也许吧 最好是我的
I don't know. Maybe. They better be mine.
甜心 再仔细想想
Sweetheart, think.
我不知道 我要回去清点我的红内裤
I don't know. I'd have to check my red panty inventory.
安迪 我要你严肃对待此事 好吗
Andie, I need you to take this seriously, okay?
这是我们最后一次相见了 直到...
This is the last time we're gonna see each other, until...
直到什么时候
Until when?
直到风平浪静
Until it's safe.
你说过要离婚的
You were going to get a divorce.
不要再大声说那事了
Never say that out loud again.
好吧 抱歉
Okay. I'm sorry.
我不想吵架
I don't wanna fight.
我只想和你在一起
I just wanna be with you.
安迪 别
Andie, please...
我别无所求
That's all I want.
现在不能
I can't.
这是我们最后一次在一起了
It's our last time together.
让我们珍惜良宵吧
Let's make the most of it.
必须快点 然后你得赶紧走
Real quick, but then you have to go.
我丈夫变得不知所措
My husband has come undone.
我们搬到密苏里来时为了救莫林
We moved to Missouri to save Maureen...
但事实证明，我们做不到
But as it turns out, we couldn't.
我们抵押掉了纽约的褐石公寓
We took a hit on the brownstone...
花光了我最后的信托基金给他买了一个酒吧
And I used the last of my trust fund to buy him a bar.
直到这，都还只是花钱
So far, it's just costing money.
尼克把我当作发泄欲望的工具
Nick uses me for sex when he wants.
除此之外，我不都存在
Otherwise, I don't exist.
今晚我们应该进城逛逛
We should go to outback tonight.
那好啊
That would be nice.
昨晚，我的心情从绝望变得凄凉
Last night, I went from desperate to pathetic.
我变成了我自己都不喜欢的人
I became someone I don't even like.
那种我从前经常嘲讽的女人
The kind of woman I used to mock.
你经常出去啊
You're out so much.
-我知道 -留在家里吧
-I know. -Stay home.
不行，我已经迟了-那我能去吗？
-I can't, I'm already late.-Then, can I come?
你不会喜欢的
You would hate it.
就是一帮白痴高中同学
It's a bunch of my dorky high school friends.
用我们的暗号保证你没有鬼扯
Do our code. No bullshit.
我曾以为我们不会成为那样的夫妻
I thought we weren't gonna be that couple.
那好吧 再见
Okay, bye.
-嘿，我一直在想 -什么？
-Hey, I've been thinking.-Yeah?
一些积极的事
Something positive.
也许现在是时候了
Maybe it's time.
现在是最不合适的时候
Now is literally the worst time.
这将会是我们新的开始
It would be a new start for us.
并且对我来说，我在这里将会有一个切实的目标
And for me,I would have a real purpose here.
带孩子可不是什么兴趣爱好
A child is not a hobby.
不是爱好
Not a hobby.
是一种动力
An inspiration.
你该早四个小时找我吵架 我要迟到了
We could have had this fight four hours ago. I'm late.
我没想到这会变成争吵
I didn't know it was gonna be a fight.
你真想要我们成为那种靠孩子来挽救婚姻的夫妻吗
You really wanna be the couple that has a baby to save their marriage?
“挽救”？
"Save"?
重启、重组、重燃 随你怎么称呼
Reboot, retool, rekindle, whatever!
-而你马上就准备破门而出 -是啊
-And you're gonna walk out the door now? -Yeah!
你这个该死的懦夫
You're a fucking coward.
不，你不能就这样走了
No, it can't go on like this.
是吗
Really?
我不允许-你不允许什么
-I won't.-You won't?
你说你不许？ 为什么 这样的生活不能满足你吗
You won't? Why, it's not good enough for you?
差得远呢！
It's not even close!
愚蠢的贱货
You stupid bitch!
吓着我的并不是他推了我
What scared mewasn't that he'd pushed me.
而是他多么想更深的伤害我
What scared me was how much he wanted to hurt me more.
是我终于意识到
What scared me was that I'd finally realized...
我害怕我自己的丈夫
I am frightened of my own husband.
要我打电话叫后援吗
You want me to call for backup?
不啦，我会保护你的
Nah, I'll protect you.
天哪
Jesus.
他们该把这地方烧了
They ought to burn this place down.
看来有家伙尝试过了
Seems like folks are trying.
到这鬼地方真有意义吗
You really think this is anything?
只是来确认一下
Cross it off the list.
嘿，杰森
Hey, Jason.
怎么了 朗达
What's up, Rhonda?
“奉行一切人生而平等的原则”
"...and dedicated to the proposition that all men..."
-你在附近见过这女孩吗 -你问这个干嘛
-Have you seen this girl around here? -Why do you ask?
有人报告她失踪了
She was reported missing.
“是否能够长久存在"
...and so dedicated, can long endure."
认识 我记得她
Yeah. I remember her.
她想要什么 大麻，摇头丸？
What did she want? Weed, pills?
她想要一把枪
She wanted a gun.
我告诉她我不做这事
I told her it's not my thing.
我也不好受 她看上去很绝望
I felt bad, though. She seemed really desperate.
她说要很小的枪 那样就能近距离开枪了
She said it needed to be small, so she could keep it close.
你确定这是她
*Are you sure this is her?
在这种鬼地方出现那种女孩可忘不了
You don't forget a girl like that in here.
她一身粉色
She was all in pink.
那天是情人节
It was Valentine's day.
今天是情人节，我以为我会买一把枪
For Valentine's day,I thought I'd buy a gun.
我现在变得多疯狂
That is how crazy I've become.
尼克想要我离开，但他不会要求离婚
Nick wants me gone but he won't ask for a divorce.
在他心中，我是他酒吧的主人，他唯一的信用额度
In his mind, I'm the owner of his bar,his only line of credit.
订下婚前协定的婊子
The bitch with the prenup.
我可以回到我父母身边
I could go home to my parents...
但我就要告诉他们事实
But I'd have to tell them the truth.
可我自己都不清楚自己是否相信这个事实
And I don't even knowif I believe the truth.
我真的可以认为尼克想要伤害我妈？
Can I really think Nick would hurt me?
我开始妄想、发疯
I'm being paranoid. Crazy.
只是
It's just...
我最好还是带把枪睡觉
I'd sleep better with a gun.
糟了
Oh, shit.
醒来了 宝贝 我姐姐要出来了
Wake up, baby. My sister's gonna come out here.
-抱歉这么催你 -没关系
-Sorry to rush you -It's okay
-在这里 我来帮你 -好了
-Here. Let me help you. -Okay.
把它穿好
Just get that.
小心点
Be very careful.
我没事
I'm all right.
给
Here you go.
答应我每天都联系
Promise me we'll talk every day.
行 我保证
Okay, we will.
每天都要 尼克 不然我还疯的
Every day, Nick, or I'll go crazy.
别疯
Don't go crazy.
好吧
Okay.
你个该死的白痴
You fucking idiot.
你个该死的混蛋  你当着老娘的面撒天操的大谎
You fucking asshole! You fucking lied to my fucking face!
对不起
I'm sorry.
她多少岁了
How old is she?
刚满二十
She's in her early 20s.
多久了
How long?
-一年半了 -你对我撒了一年半的谎？
-A year and a half. -You lied to me for over a year?
如果我告诉你 你会制止我的
If I told you, you would have made me stop.
小人一个
It's so fucking small.
你说谎 背叛 就和爸爸一个德行
You're a liar and a cheat! You're just like dad!
你是怎么认识她的
How did you even meet her?
她是我的学生
She's one of my students.
我以为作家讨厌这样狗血的故事
I thought writers hated clichés.
我不是作家
I'm not a writer.
呜呜 我被炒了 我猜我得上个年轻女孩
"Boo-hoo, I got laid off. I guess I'll fuck a teenager."
不是你想的那样 好吗 你不知道和艾米生活有多受罪
It wasn't like that, okay? You have no idea how shitty it was with Amy...
她让我感觉多他妈的可怕
How fucking terrible she made me feel.
一想到刚回家 甚至还未踏进那破屋
Flyover boy. I would get knots in my stomach...
她就端坐在那里 摆着一副臭脸
Just coming home, knowing she would be sitting there...
我的胃简直要纠作一团
Dissatisfied, before I even walked in the fucking door.
这处境太糟糕了
This is so bad.
如果被任何人发现 你就死定了
If anybody finds out, you're totally fucked.
邦尼在我办公室发现了一条内裤
Boney found a pair of panties in my office...
安迪和我偶尔在那里...
Where, occasionally, Andie and I...
我不知道这他妈的意味着什么
I don't know what the fuck it means.
他们是超级贱逼吗
Are they super-twat's?
她名字是安迪
Her name is Andie.
她也不十分肯定
She's not entirely sure.
所以我们面对的是一个...
So we are dealing with a 20-year-old...
连自己内裤都不知道脱在哪里的二十岁女孩
Who isn't sure where she leaves her undies?
如果内裤不是安迪的 那就说明是艾米自己的
If they're not Andie's, that means that they're Amy's...
故意放在那里等我去找
And she left them there for me to find.
尼克 以前我就有点怕你 现在我他妈的已经彻底石化了
Nick, I was scared for you before, and now, I'm fucking petrified.
今晚我们要为你失踪的妻子守夜
We're having a vigil tonight for your missing wife...
而在同一天早上 你在吻别你的大学生女友
And this morning, you're kissing your college girlfriend goodbye!
你能想象吗
Can you imagine?
你最近有看电视吗
Have you watched television lately?
有线新闻全在报道你的破事
Cable news is all over your shit.
我想说 这个酒吧老板是有什么毛病
I mean, what is wrong with this barkeep?
他的妻子无处可寻
His wife's nowhere to be found...
这位先生却还在这张可爱的照片上调情
And here's Nick dunne for you, flirting. Cute pic, huh?
-那是谁 -某个可悲的追星少女
-Who is that? -Some fucking tragedy groupie.
-她是哪里杀出来的 -我不知道
她要给我做派来着
She was trying to give me a casserole.
今天的节目中我们有幸请到了辩护律师坦纳.博尔特
On the show today we have defense attorney, Tanner bolt...
各地杀妻凶手的守护神
Patron Saint to wife-killers everywhere.
坦纳.博尔特 你真的要为尼克.道恩辩护吗
Tanner bolt, would you actually consider defending Nick dunne?
还是那句老生常谈
Well, let me just say...
艾伦 谢谢你如此热情地介绍我
As always, Ellen, thank you for such a warm welcome.
当然我会为尼克.道恩辩护
But of course, I'd defend Nick dunne.
听着 原因是这个人没有边走边痛哭流涕
Listen, just because this guy isn't walking around weeping...
并不代表他内心没有受伤
That doesn't mean that he's not hurting.
坦纳 缺乏同情心是反社会者的突出特征
Tanner, the hallmark of a sociopath is a lack of empathy.
但事实是 如果在这种处境下
But the truth is, you'd have to be a sociopath...
表现得正常就太反社会了
To behave normally in this situation...
因为这是世界上最反常的处境
Because it's the most abnormal situation in the world.
坦纳 你是想告诉我这张照片所揭露的行为
Tanner, are you trying to tell me that this photo...
属于正常人可以接受的范围吗
Is remotely in the realm of acceptable behavior?
我受够了被女人这样指手画脚
I'm so sick of being picked apart by women.
你得雇坦纳.博尔特了
You need to hire Tanner bolt.
我不该到落到这步田地
I don't deserve this.
这是无罪推定
Innocent until proven guilty.
你就该遭这报应
That's exactly what you deserve.
回去吧 尼克
Go home, Nick.
嘿 老弟
Hey, buddy.
真不敢相信我们竟没逮捕这家伙
I can't believe we haven't arrested this guy.
我们不会因为某个金发碧眼的傻瓜的胡说
We're not gonna arrest anybody...
就去逮捕任何人
Just because some blonde dunce says so.
你为什么为他开脱 你爱上他了吗
Why are you going so easy on him? You got a crush?
首先 我是在办案 不是猎巫婆
One, I am conducting an investigation, not a witch-hunt.
其次 永远不要再用那种语气和我讲话了
And, two, don't talk to me that way, ever.
她可是想要买把枪
She was trying to buy a gun.
我们不知道是什么人什么事在惊吓她 吉尔
We don't know who or what was scaring her, gil.
汇报最新调查情况
Give me the update.
目前没发现吸毒的可能 把它划掉了
No drug angles panned out yet, so cross that off the list.
我也询问了照料尼克父亲的护士
I talked to the nurses who care for Nick's father.
那家伙虽然很混蛋 但虚弱得像只小猫 也从名单上划掉了
The guy's a bastard, but he's weak as a kitten, so cross that off the list.
发光氨测试结果显示厨房的血迹是七月四日的
So, luminol lit up the kitchen like the 4th of July.
血迹相当多
The blood is profuse.
是艾米的 B型 我们很快就能提取DNA了
It is Amy's, type b, and we should have DNA soon.
凶器呢？
Thoughts on a weapon?
痕迹表明是钝物重击所致
Trajectory indicates blunt force.
也许是球棍 或是小木棒
Maybe a club or a two-by-four.
她倒下了 但我怀疑她又站起来了
She fell there, but I doubt she got back up.
艾米的医疗记录拿到了吗
Amy's medical records come in?
还没有 晚些时候能拿到
No, we'll have them later tonight.
我妻子说他是凶手
My wife says he's a killer.
好吧 如果蒂凡尼那样说...
Well, if Tiffany says...
唐尼 你还好吗
Hey Donnie, how are you?
里克 非常感谢你
Rich, thank you so much.
谢谢大家 感谢你们今晚能到这里来
Thank you, folks. Thank you for being here tonight.
这对我们的家庭来说意义十分重大
It just means the world to our family.
对艾米也是
And to Amy.
如大家所知
As you all know...
我的妻子 艾米.艾略特.道恩
My wife, Amy elliott dunne...
三天前失踪了
Disappeared three days ago.
我诚挚地恳求任何知道相关消息的人
And I want to implore anyone who has any information at all...
请站出来 帮助我们
Please come forward. Help us.
太性感了
So hot.
他太可怕了
He is so creepy.
我想说几句 因为我知道你们中有些人很疑惑
I wanna say something, because I think some of you might be wondering...
但出于礼貌不便发问
And are too polite to ask.
我与我妻子的失踪没有任何关系
I had nothing to do with the disappearance of my wife.
我在同警方竭诚合作
I'm cooperating with the police.
我也没有雇律师
I haven't hired a lawyer.
我没有任何事情需要隐瞒
I have nothing to hide.
艾米是我的灵魂伴侣
Amy is my soul mate.
她美丽
She is brilliant...
迷人 聪慧
She's charming, and wise.
我爱你 艾米
I love you, Amy.
混蛋
Asshole.
我爱我的妻子
I love my wife...
全心全意
So much.
我也许没有在镜头前故作姿态 如媒体所期望的那样
And I may not behave for the cameras the way they want me to...
如果他们想为此惩罚我 那无所谓
And if they wanna punish me for that, that's okay.
但我想恳求那些造谣者 请来骚扰我
But I just wanna ask you in the media, please, harass me...
不要去骚扰这里的其他人
But don't harass the people of this town.
如果你们要嘲弄人 尽管嘲弄我
If you need to mock somebody, mock me.
尼克！
Nick!
但请不要把案件调查当做儿戏
But please don't turn this investigation into a circus.
你的妻子在哪里 尼克
Where's your wife, Nick?
让警察去做他们的工作
Let the police do their jobs
你对你怀孕的妻子做了什么
What did you do to your pregnant wife?
你告诉他们了吗 尼克
Did you tell them that, Nick?
你告诉他们她已有六周身孕了吗
Did you tell them Amy was six weeks pregnant?
感谢大家今晚前来支持 让我们共同寻找艾米吧
Thank you for your support tonight. Let's find Amy.
继续吧 如果你们想说点什么
Go ahead, if you guys wanna say something.
尼克 你要去哪里
Nick, where are you going?
拦住他
Stop him!
现在不接受提问 谢谢
No questions right now. Thank you.
你为什么急着逃跑
Why are you running away?
不要跑
Don't run.
所有人都靠后
Everybody, stay back.
好了 你们知道规矩的
Guys, come on. You know better.
不要接近草地，退到路边去
Get off the grass, get down to the curb.
-嘿，吉尔 -好的
-Hey, gil... -On it.
好的 你们都听到了 不要拍照
All right, y'all heard her. No pictures.
谁
Hello?
谁啊
操
Fuck.
你吓到我了 要来一杯吗
You scared me. Want a drink?
你知道她怀孕了吗？
Did you know she was pregnant?
我告诉你了 诺艾尔.霍桑是他妈个疯子
I told you, noelle hawthorne is fucking crazy.
她甚至不认识艾米
She doesn't even know Amy.
我看她们好得很呢
They look like pretty good friends to me.
听着 我根本不知道 而且这也证明不了她怀孕了
Look, I don't know. But it certainly doesn't prove that she's pregnant.
我们很快就能拿到她的医检报告了
We have her medical records coming.
-很好 -那么 趁等待的空闲谈谈吧
-Good. -So, let's talk while we wait.
我们就从这开始吧，这个犯罪现场
Let's start over here.The scene of the crime.
你知道吗，我们处理过很多起室内入侵案件
You see, we've seen dozens of home invasions.
数不胜数
Dozens and dozens.
这一块区域，我一看到就觉得有问题
This area right here, it looked wrong from the second we saw it.
所有的东西都像是刻意布置过的，你看
The whole thing looked staged. Watch this.
在经过这场生死搏斗后还保持的好端端的？
And yet, they remained upright throughout this life-and-death struggle?
我不知道 你想要我说什么
I don't know. What do you want me to say?
你妻子失踪的那天你有打扫屋子吗
Did you do any housekeeping the day your wife went missing?
没有
No.
发光氨测试：用以鉴别经过擦洗，时间很久的血痕
因为我们的人做了一个发光氨测试
Because our guys did a luminol test.
并且我很遗憾的告诉你，厨房里亮得不行
And I'm sorry to tell you,but that kitchen lit up.
艾米在厨房失了很多血，尼克，很多
Amy lost a lot of blood in there, Nick. A lot.
我的天
Oh, my God.
对，然后有人把它擦干净了
Yeah, and then somebody mopped it up.
等等 如果他们想要制造犯罪现场
Wait a second. Why would they mop up the blood...
为什么他们还要把血拖掉
If they're trying to stage a crime scene?
没有血迹，没有尸体，表明是绑架
No blood and no body suggests kidnapping.
这告诉我们，要调查屋外的人
It tells us, look at people outside the house.
就比如你一直在强调的流浪汉
Like these homeless you keep mentioning.
空有一滩血而没有尸体则意味着是凶杀案
A pool of blood and no body suggests homicide.
这告诉我们调查屋内的人
It tells us to look at people inside the house.
-我们来这儿就是为了这个，尼克 -我明白了
-Which is what we're doing here, Nick. -I see.
所以，你的婚姻怎样，尼克？因为我们目前只有诺艾尔一面之词
So, how was your marriage, Nick?  Because right now, all we got is noelle.
她说“不太好”
She says, "not good."
吉尔 你和你妻子会争论什么？
Gil, what do you and your wife argue about?
-都是什么惹你们吵架 -钱呗 缺钱
-What pisses you off? -Money, lack thereof.
我和我前夫也是这样
Me and my ex, it's the same.
我提到这个事因为我们调查了一下你的财务状况，尼克
I mention that because we got a look at your finances, Nick.
11.7万美元的信用卡欠款
$117,000 in credit card debt.
-什么？-我查看了一些你买的东西
-What?-I pulled up some of the merchandise.
就是这些小小的挥霍
There are these fun little splurges.
我根本没买过这些东西
I didn't buy any of this stuff.
我根本不打高尔夫
I don't even golf!
我打，你买的是很好的球杆
I do! You bought great clubs.
我喜欢机器狗
I like the robot dog.
这是身份盗窃 这是重罪
This is identity theft! This is a felony!
我们需要查出这是谁干的
We need to find out who did this!
好了，我们来谈谈这份保险吧
All right. Let's talk about life insurance.
因为在四月，你把艾米的人寿保险
Because in April, you bumped up Amy's life insurance...
提到了120万美元
To $1.2 million.
我的确做过 那是她的主意 她叫我那样做
Yes, I did. That was her idea. She wanted me to.
你填了这些文件
You filed the paperwork.
因为她叫我签
Because she told me to!
等等
Hold on a sec.
什么？好的
Yeah? Okay.
确定？
For sure?
好
All right.
她怀孕了
She was pregnant..
这太疯狂了
This is insane.
所以，我的问题现在是
So, my question becomes-
我不想再和你谈话了
I don't want to talk to you again, ever...
除非有律师在场
Without a lawyer.
玛格
Margo!
等一等 让我说完
Just hold on a second. Let me finish.
尼克
Nick?
我听到了 我听到了 我也很惊讶
I hear you, I hear you. I was as surprised as--
我知道你很生沮丧 我也不知道她怀孕了
I know you're upset. I had no idea she was pregnant.
我也这样想过 但显然并不是...
Listen, I thought so, too, but evidently that wasn't--
你想知道真相吗
you want to know the truth?
真相是 艾米不想要孩子
The truth is, Amy didn't want kids.
是的 我也很震惊
Well, I'm as surprised as--
你告诉过我是你不想要孩子
you told me you didn't want kids.
我只是想说着好听点
I was trying to put a good face on.
所以突然间 你就有了个怀孕的妻子
Then, suddenly, you've got a pregnant wife.
这成大问题了
That's a problem for you.
尤其是把你的秘密年轻女友也考虑在内
Especially when you factor in the secret teenage girlfriend.
别看艾伦.阿伯特的脑残节目了
Oh, stop watching Ellen abbott!
那你他妈就告诉我事实
You have to fucking talk to me!
我没有告诉你她不想要孩子 因为她不想要别人知道
I didn't tell you that she didn't want kids because she didn't want me to.
因为那只会成为另一条你讨厌她的理由
Because it would have just been another reason for you to hate her.
理由已经够多了 所以我干脆就...
And we had enough of those already! It was easier to just--
-说谎？ -操 我想要孩子！
-lie to me? -I wanted kids!
我们刚搬来的时候 我还进了生育诊所
When we first moved here, I went to a fertility clinic!
-没凑效？ -该干的我都干了
-It didn't work? -I did my part!
继续撸
Masturbate.
轮到艾米表态时 她突然就变卦了
When it came time for Amy to do her thing, all of a sudden it was like...
“嗯，我有点顾虑 也许算了吧... 谢了”
"Well, I don't know. Maybe. No, thanks."
现在谁会相信你
Now, who would believe you?
好吧
All right.
这是诊所的一封信
This is a letter from the clinic...
通知我说尽快和他们联系
Notifying me that they're gonna destroy my sample...
否则就销毁我的精子
Unless I contact them.
然后我把信给艾米看
So, I gave it to Amy.
第二天 我在垃圾桶发现了它
The next day, I saw it in the trash.
但那时你已经和安迪好上了 不是吗
But you were already with Andie by then, right?
可我想和艾米生小孩啊
I wanted a baby with Amy.
一年前 艾米怀孕会是我能想象出的最好的事
A year ago, Amy being pregnant would have been the best thing ever!
“当你可怜的艾米一得了感冒 这些甜品就得--”
"When your poor Amy has a cold, this dessert just--"
这是你没有解开的线索
this is the clue you couldn't solve.
是啊
Yeah.
来自德西的信 艾米那个变态前男友？
A letter from desi. That creepy boyfriend of Amy's?
就是那个愿意为艾米吃屎的该死土豪
It was the fucking rich guy who would do anything for her.
阴魂不散 太恶心了
It just kept hanging over my head. It was disgusting.
你的婚前协议？
Your prenup?
尼克 你干嘛留着这些 这像是个装满仇恨的小盒
Nick, why have you kept this stuff? It's like a little box of hate.
不知道 也许我就是恨她
I don't know, go! Maybe I hate her!
不管怎样我都爱你
I love you no matter what.
但你必须告诉我
But you need to tell me.
告诉你什么
Tell you what?
你想问我什么
What are you asking me?
你想问我是不是谋杀了我妻子吗 格？
Are you asking me if I killed my wife, go?
你是在问我这个吗 我有没有谋杀我妻子
Is that what you're asking me? If I murdered my wife?
我绝不会问你那样的问题
I would never ask you that!
玛格
Margo!
别在玻璃上走
Don't walk on the glass.
你身上没线索 对吧?
You have no clue, do you?
他昨晚为什么来这里
Why was he here that night?
他妻子失踪了？他为什么来这？
His wife is missing. Why come here?
管他呢
Who cares?
朗达 我们已经破案了
Rhonda, we got this.
把他抓起来吧
Let's make the arrest.
你知道在没有尸体的情况下立一个谋杀案有多困难吗？
Do you know how hard it is to make a murder case without a body?
不知道
No.
那真是相当难
Well, it's incredibly hard.
所以，我还要最后一样东西
So, I want one last thing.
是什么
What's that?
尸体
I want a body.
想象我是个很坏很坏的女孩
Picture me. I'm a girl who's very, very bad.
我需要被惩罚 被惩罚 我是说 活该
I need to be punished, and by "punished," I mean "had."
该死
Fuck.
那就是你存放五周年纪念礼物的地方
It's where you keep goodies for anniversary five.
所以，打开那道门吧
So, open the door...
惩罚 木头 河滩
Punish. Wood. Beach.
好好看吧
...and look alive.
惩罚 木头
Punish. Wood.
木头
Wood.
我会试着去相信我的丈夫是爱我的
I will practice believing my husband loves me...
并且也会爱这个孩子
And will love this baby.
这个孩子也许真的能拯救我的婚姻
That this child might really save our marriage.
但也可能是我想错了
But I could be wrong.
因为有时候...
Because sometimes...
他看我的眼神...
The way he looks at me...
我觉得...
I think...
我梦想中的男人
Man of my dreams...
我孩子的父亲
Father of my child...
这个属于我的男人可能会杀了我
This man of mine may kill me.
他可能真的会
He may truly...
杀了我
Kill me.
什么鬼
Wtf?
我死了，现在我开心了许多
I am so much happier now that I'm dead.
准确地说，是”失踪“
Technically, "missing."
很快就会被认定成死亡
Soon to be presumed dead.
消失
Gone.
而我那懒散，虚伪，不忠的丈夫
And my lazy, lying, cheating, oblivious husband...
将会因谋杀我而身陷囹圄
Will go to prison for my murder.
尼克道恩夺走了我的骄傲和尊严
Nick dunne took my pride and my dignity...
我的希望和金钱
And my hope and my money.
他不停地从我这里夺取，直到夺取我的存在
He took and took from me until I no longer existed.
这就是谋杀
That's murder.
让他受到应有的惩罚
Let the punishment fit the crime.
伪造一场令人信服的谋杀案，你需要严密计划
To fake a convincing murder, you have to have discipline.
和当地的白痴交朋友
You befriend a local idiot.
倾听她乏味生活的碎屑杂事
Harvest the details of her humdrum life.
并给她灌输揭示你丈夫火爆脾气的故事
And cram her with stories about your husband's violent temper.
秘密地制造一些财政问题
Secretly create some money troubles.
信用卡，或许是网上赌博
Credit cards, perhaps online gambling.
在酒精的推动下
With the help of the unwitting...
提高你的人寿保险金
Bump up your life insurance.
买一辆逃跑用的车，当然是在网上找
Purchase getaway car. Craigslist.
普通的，便宜的，现金支付
Generic. Cheap. Pay cash.
你需要给人们留下好印象，这样人们才会为你的逝去而哀悼
You need to package yourself so that people will truly mourn your loss.
美国人对孕妇充满爱心
And America loves pregnant women.
好像分开双腿很是件难事一样
As if it's so hard to spread your legs.
你知道什么是难事吗？
You know what's hard?
伪造怀孕
Faking a pregnancy.
第一步，抽干你的马桶
First, drain your toilet.
邀请怀孕的白痴来你家做客
Invite pregnant idiot into your home...
给她下柠檬水
And ply her with lemonade.
取一些这个怀孕傻瓜的尿液
Steal pregnant idiot's urine.
好了
Voilà.
现在怀孕就会出现在你的医检报告
A pregnancy is now part of your legal medical record.
纪念日快乐(￣_,￣ )
Happy anniversary.
现在只要等待你愚蠢的丈夫
Wait for your clueless husband...
开始他的一天
To start his day.
他走了
Off he goes.
计时开始
And the clock is ticking.
一丝不苟地布置你的犯罪现场
Meticulously stage your crime scene...
只要留下一些足够引起怀疑的错误
With just enough mistakes to raise the specter of doubt.
你需要流血（出血量超大Σ( ° △ °|||)︴)
You need to bleed.
很多
A lot.
很多，很多（出血量超大Σ( ° △ °|||)︴)
A lot, a lot.
像头上的伤口流的血
A head wound kind of bleed.
像是犯罪现场流的血
A crime scene kind of bleed.
你需要草草打扫一下
You need to clean poorly...
像他会做的那样
Like he would.
打扫、流血，流血、打扫
Clean and bleed. Bleed and clean.
并且留一点小惊喜
And leave a little something behind.
夏日生火？
A fire in July?
因为你就是你
And because you're you...
所以你不在这里止步
You don't stop there.
你需要一本日记
You need a diary.
至少有300篇关于尼克和艾米的故事
Minimum, 300 entries on the Nick and Amy story.
一开始就像童话故事一样
Start with the fairy tale early days.
那些都是真实的，并且极其重要
Those are true. And they're crucial.
你希望尼克和艾米招人喜爱
You want Nick and Amy to be likeable.
在那之后，你开始编造
After that, you invent.
挥霍
The spending.
虐待，恐惧
The abuse. The fear.
暴力的威胁
The threat of violence.
尼克还自诩为作家呢
And Nick thought he was the writer.
把日记烧的恰到好处
Burn it just the right amount.
确保警察能找到它
Make sure the cops will find it.
最后，遵照传统，附上一个特别的寻宝活动
Finally, honor tradition with a very special treasure hunt.
如果我没搞错的话，全世界都将痛恨尼克
And if I get everything right, the world will hate Nick...
因他杀害了他美丽的，怀有身孕的妻子
For killing his beautiful, pregnant wife.
在这一切愤慨消散之后，我会做好准备
And after all the outrage, when I'm ready...
我将服几粒药丸 用一袋石头缚着我
I'll go out on the water with a handful of pills...
沉入海底
And a pocket full of stones.
当他们找到我的尸体时，他们就会知道
And when they find my body, they'll know...
尼克道恩把他挚爱的妻子像垃圾一样遗弃了
Nick dunne dumped his beloved like garbage.
她一路漂流，经过所有其他
And she floated down past all the other...
被虐待，遗弃，碍眼的女人
Abused, unwanted, inconvenient women.
之后，尼克也将去死
Then, Nick will die, too.
尼克和艾米都会消失
Nick and Amy will be gone.
不过，之后，我们从没真正存在
But, then, we never really existed.
尼克爱的是我当时假装的那个人
Nick loved a girl I was pretending to be.
“酷女孩”
"Cool girl."
男人总是用这个作为他们最高的恭维
Men always use that as their defining compliment.
“她是个很酷的女孩”
"She's a cool girl."
酷女孩是性感的
Cool girl is hot.
酷女孩是随性的
Cool girl is game.
酷女孩是有趣的
Cool girl is fun.
酷女孩从来不会对她的男人生气
Cool girl never gets angry at her man.
她只是带着苦恼和忠于礼节的微笑
She only smiles in a chagrined, loving manner...
并且她们乐于给他人口交
And then presents her mouth for fucking.
她喜欢他喜欢的一切
She likes what he likes.
所以，很显然，他是一个喜欢色情漫画的嬉皮士
So evidently, he's a vinyl hipster who loves fetish manga.
如果他喜欢狂野的女孩，她是个
If he likes girls gone wild, she's a mall babe...
会谈论橄榄球和喜欢在猫头鹰餐厅吃水牛城辣鸡翅的女孩
Who talks football and endures buffalo wings at Hooters.
我认识尼克道恩的时候，我就知道他想要一个酷女孩
When I met Nick dunne, I knew he wanted cool girl.
为了他，我承认，我愿意尝试
And for him, I'll admit, I was willing to try.
我除了我的阴毛
I wax-stripped my pussy raw.
我喝灌装啤酒，看亚当桑德勒的电影
I drank canned beer watching Adam sandler movies.
我吃冷冻披萨可我还是穿2号的衣服
I ate cold pizza and remained a size two.
我时不时还给他吹
I blew him semi-regularly.
我活在当下
I lived in the moment.
我他妈就是适应
I was fucking game.
我不能说这些我都不喜欢
I can't say I didn't enjoy some of it.
尼克把我身上连我自己都不知道的东西给勾了出来
Nick teased out of me things I didn't know existed.
轻松，幽默和安逸
A lightness, a humor, an ease.
但我也把他变得更聪明，敏锐
But I made him smarter. Sharper
我激励了他到达我的层次
I inspired him to rise to my level.
我造就了我梦想中的男人
I forged the man of my dreams.
我们都很高兴地装成他人
We were happy pretending to be other people.
我们是最幸福的夫妻
We were the happiest couple we knew.
如果不是最幸福的，那在一起还有什么意义？
And what's the point of being together if you're not the happiest?
但尼克变懒了
But Nick got lazy.
他变成了我不想与之结婚的那种人
He became someone I did not agree to marry.
事实上，他希望我能够无条件的爱他
He actually expected me to love him unconditionally.
然后他拉着身无分文的我来到这个国家的中心
Then he dragged me, penniless, to the navel of this great country...
然后给他自己找了个更新、年轻、有活力的
And found himself a newer, younger, bouncier...
酷女孩
Cool girl.
你以为我会让他就这样摧毁我然后比以往都幸福地活下去吗？
You think I'd let him destroy me and end up happier than ever?
他妈没门
No fucking way.
他赢不了
He doesn't get to win.
我可爱、迷人、带着泥土气息的密苏里男孩
My cute, charming, salt-of-the-earth, Missouri guy.
他要知道
He needed to learn.
成年人是要玩手段的
Grown-ups work for things.
成年人是要付出代价的
Grown-ups pay.
成年人要承担后果
Grown-ups suffer consequences.
等等
Wait.
给我二十秒时间 不要评判我或者打断我
I need 20 seconds where you don't judge me, interrupt me...
也不要生气
Or get angry.
好吧
Okay.
信用卡账单上的东西都在这里吗
Is that all the stuff from the credit cards?
五周年纪念日的东西你都放在哪了
Where do you store goodies for anniversary five?
木婚
Wood.
-木屋 -在我的木屋
-Woodshed. -Yeah, my woodshed.
该死的婊子
That fucking bitch.
-我本以为...  -没关系
-I thought-- -it's all right.
换我也会这么想
I would have, too.
那礼物是什么
What's that present?
不知道
I don't know.
打开看看吧
Let's find out.
“亲爱的丈夫，我知道你以为你的行为神不知鬼不觉
"Dear husband, I know you think you're moving through this world unseen.
“不要再迷信你自己了”
"Don't believe that for a second.
“我知道你去过哪里，以及你将要去哪里”
"I know where you've been, and I know where you're going."
“今年的纪念日，我安排了一场旅行
"For this anniversary, I've arranged a trip.
“沿着河流 一直向上
"Follow the river, up, up, up.
“坐好，放松，因为你就要完蛋了”
"Sit back and relax, because you are done."
什么是“顺流而上”？
What's "up, up river"?
“河的上游”，监狱
"Up the river." Prison.
他妈的疯婊子
Fucking crazy bitch.
原来是这样
That's what this is.
她把我套进谋杀罪里了
She's framing me for her murder.
你娶了一个真正的变态
You married a complete psychopath.
结婚纪念日的早上
The morning of our anniversary...
我想跟她提出离婚 我实在不能忍受了
I was gonna ask her for a divorce. I just couldn't do it.
我不能再这样假装着过一年 一天都不想
I couldn't fake it for another year, another day.
然后发生了什么
Then what happened?
在我还没张口之前 她说
Before I could say anything, she said...
”我希望你能到什么地方静一静 好好思考下我们的婚姻“
"I need you to go somewhere and really think about our marriage."
她知道我会去索耶沙滩
She knew I would go to Sawyer beach.
那样你就没有不在场证明了
So you'd have no alibi.
她幕后艹纵着我
She stage-managed me.
她完全知道我会怎么做 而我真他妈那样做了
She knew exactly what I would do . And I fucking did it
我去了沙滩 思考了我们的婚姻
I went to the beach, I thought about our marriage.
我回去 决定提出离婚
I came back and decided I wanted a divorce.
结果当你跨进家门时
And by the time you got home--
她失踪了
she was gone.
作孽啊
You fuck!
真有她大的
She's good.
部分的我感觉得到了解脱
Part of me was relieved...
当我想到她已经不在之后
When I thought she was gone.
潘趣与朱迪的木偶
Punch and Judy puppets.
记得吗 他打死了朱迪又杀死了小孩
Remember, he beats Judy to death and kills that baby.
所以我是潘趣吗
So I'm punch.
这我们都知道了 艾米 你想表达什么
We already knew that, Amy, what's your point?
密苏里州有死刑吗
Does Missouri have the death penalty?
嘿，邻居
Hey, neighbor.
我已经好几个 星期没见到像样的邻居了
It's been weeks since I had anyone decent next door.
那个，我不知道怎样才是得体
Well, I don't know how decent I feel.
只要你不养蟒蛇并在凌晨四点放死亡重金属就行
As long as you don't own a python and blast death metal at 4 am...
我们会成为好朋友的
We're gonna be best friends.
好啊，很高兴见到你
All right. Nice meeting you.
我叫格丽塔
I'm greta.
我叫南希
I'm Nancy.
你要去码头吗？我可以抹防晒霜
Are you going to the marina? I could use some creamer.
对不起，不用
I'm sorry. I can't.
我还有事要做
I've got work to do.
好的，那回见
All right. See you around!
一定
You will.
来啊，露出你那亲爱的尼克式的微笑
Come on. Show me that darling Nicky smile.
你个混蛋
You asshole.
嘿
Hey.
南希
Nancy.
今天又热了
It's hot again today.
你从哪来？
So, where are you from?
让我猜猜
Let me guess.
内布拉斯加
Nebraska.
新奥尔良
New Orleans.
你知道吗，我课是涂油专家
You know, I am an expert oiler.
噢，那是
Oh, I just bet you are.
乳霜，软膏，油膏
Lotions and balms. Ointment.
我可不想你被晒黑
I would hate for y'all to get tan lines.
真贴心
So sweet.
好了，你知道我会在哪
Okay. You know where I'll be.
我看我们对男人的品味一样
I see we have the same taste in men.
我把它贴在浴室柜门上了
I clipped it on a bathroom cabinet.
至少你可以做到不要对他保守秘密
Least you could do is not keep his secrets for him.
让我猜猜
Let me guess.
他老师打游戏，而你就一直唠叨
He's trying to watch the big game and you just won't shut up.
不，你看起来不想个会唠叨的人
No, you don't seem like much of a talker.
我知道了
I got it.
你发现你点男人和小骚货乱搞
You caught your boy rubbing up on some hot little skank...
他不但不道歉还打了你一顿
And he apologized to you by busting you a good one.
比这跟糟
Worse.
更糟？
Worse?
我去他工作的酒吧想给他一个惊喜
I went to the bar where he works to surprise him.
而他就跟一个甚至还不能进酒吧的女孩站在外面
And out he comes with this girl who had no business being in a bar.
我们遇见的第一个晚上
On the very first night that we met...
我们走过一个正在卸载糖粉的面包房
We walked by a bakery that was having their sugar delivered.
糖粉飘散在空中，到处都是
And it was in the air, everywhere.
真是一场甜蜜的风暴
A sugar storm.
在他亲吻我之前
And before he kissed me...
我弯下身子
He leaned in...
然后做了这个动作
And did this.
你猜怎么了？ -怎么了？
-And guess what. -What?
他跟那个女孩做了一模一样的事
He did the exact same thing with her.
那真是我听说过最恶心的事了
That is the most disgusting thing I ever heard.
谢谢你
Thank you.
非常感谢
Thanks very much.
我们成焦点了
Well, we've gone mainstream.
这是上诉流程，我们会起诉他们
It's an appeals process, so we will attempt to appeal to them.
博尔特先生 坦纳博尔特
Mr. bolt. Tanner bolt?
尼克道恩
Nick dunne.
我一直在等你的电话，我的朋友
I have been sitting by the phone, my friend.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
你不相信我吗
Do you not believe me?
不，我当然相信你，只是这真是我听过最疯狂的事
No, I believe you. It's just the craziest thing I've ever heard.
我很喜欢这个故事，但是，对你来说，糟透了
I love it. But, for you, it sucks.
不过你在这一点上必须要佩服你的妻子，不是吗？
But you gotta have a grudging respect for your wife at this point, right?
-你想用嘲笑把我从这楼里送出去吗 -不
-Are you laughing me out of the building? -No!
你在开玩笑吗？我干了
Are you kidding me? I'm in.
这活我干了
I'm way in.
你找对人了伙计，我就是干这个的，尼克
You came to the right guy. This is what I do, Nick.
这就是为什么我要收10万的预付款，没有我打不赢的官司
This is why I have a $100,000 retainer. I win the unwinnable cases.
我们能解决的
We'll figure something out.
我会给你一个特别的
I'll give you a special...
“我妻子精通复仇艺术”的优惠
"My wife is skilled in the art of vengeance" rate.
好吧
Okay.
那么 接下来怎么办
So, what's the plan?
现在呢，就是“他说过，她说过”啰
Well, right now, it's a "he said, she said."
-她讲的故事比我好 -不 尼克
-She's telling a better story. -No, Nick.
她讲的是一个完美的故事
She is telling the perfect story.
所以，我们需要从现在开始准备你的辩词，会用到的
So, we need to start today to prepare your defense, should we need it.
-所以如果我们决定准备你的版本的... -真相
-And if we decide to go with your version of-- -the truth.
那我们就需要重塑一下大众对艾米的印象
Then we'll need to realign the public's perception of Amy.
让他们不再把他看做美国甜心
Make them stop seeing her as America's sweetheart...
而是看到她的本质，一个艹纵思想一等的臭婊子
And see her for what she is, which a mind-fucker of the first degree.
现在看来，那是一个巨大的变化，我们还需要其他人的声音
Now, that is a huge realignment. We'll need other voices besides yours.
某个她过去祸害过的家伙
There has to be someone out there that she's screwed with in the past.
纽约有个家伙 奥哈拉 汤米奥哈拉
There's a New York guy. O'Hara, Tommy O'Hara.
八年前 她起诉过他
Eight years ago, she pressed charges against him.
那应该很容易找到
That should be easy to find.
曾经的同学 德西.科林斯斯
Ex-classmate, desi collings.
她说他跟踪过她 他住在圣路易斯
She said that he stalked her. He's in St. Louis.
你去和汤米谈，我去起草合同
You go talk to Tommy, and I'll draw up the contract.
我给你说过，你找对人了
I told you, you came to the right guy.
好像没假
Apparently.
汤米
Tommy?
是我
Yeah.
-谢谢你来见我 -没事 没事
-Thanks for seeing me. -Yeah, yeah, yeah.
喝一杯吗
You're gonna want a drink.
她说你对她使用过暴力
So, she said you got physical with her.
不，伙计，她说我强奸了她
No, dude, she said I raped her.
一级重罪，强奸
First degree, felony rape.
-你做了吗 -你呢
-Did you do it? -Did you do it?
我面对的是30年到终身监禁
I was looking at 30 years to life.
-你有被审讯过吗 -妈的 没有
-Did you get a trial? -Fuck, no.
我看起来像从里面出来人吗？
Do I look like I would do well in the yard?
我为自己辩护了，伙计，性骚扰，不判刑
I pled down, man. Sexual assault one, no jail time.
-也不算小事了 -是啊
-That's something.-Oh, yeah.
我过去八年一直没有工作
I've been unemployed for the last eight years...
因为我得在我的每一份申请表上写上“性侵犯”
Because I have to write "sexual offender" on every job application.
我在我那个街区的监视名单上，因为我被登记为“捕猎者”
I'm on a neighborhood watch list, because I have to register as a predator.
我差不多10年没有约会过了，因为只要女孩google我
I haven't had a date in almost a decade, because if a girl googles me...
你能告诉我到底发生了什么吗
Could you walk me through what happened?
我在这个派对上面遇到的艾米，你知道吗
I meet Amy at this party, you know?
我们一拍即合，她真是太完美了
We click. She's perfect.
她美丽，聪明，魔血
She's beautiful, she's smart, she's well-read...
她有个20岁脱衣女郎的翘屁股
She's got an ass like a 20-year-old stripper.
我想“有什么目的？”
I think, "what's the catch?"
几个月后，我知道了，这不会那么轻松
A few months, it hits me. This is not going to be easy.
姑娘就像需要修缮的房子，但艾米？
Girls like a fixer-upper, but Amy?
她控制了我，把我玩得团团转
She annexed me. She made me her business.
太过了，她出去给我买条领带
It was just too much. She went out and bought me ties.
我们都要跑20趟
And we must have gone 20 rounds over that.
就几条领带，这一切都变得
Ties. The whole thing just became
-所以你和他分手了 -没 我只是躲着她
-so, you broke up with her. -No, I just backed away.
给她一点空间，没什么大不了的，是吧？
Gave her some space. No big deal, right?
所以我想
So I thought.
然后有一天，艾米来到我的住处
Then one night, Amy comes over to my place...
带着一瓶波本威士忌，还有一张我喜欢乐队的盗版盘
With a bottle of bourbon and a bootleg of this band I love.
就两分钟，她就把我内裤褪到了脚踝
And within two minutes, she's got my pants around my ankles...
然后她跪到地上，然后
And she is kneeling down, and--
对不起，我知道她是你妻子
I'm sorry. I know it's your wife.
-你们做爱了 -对 两厢情愿
-You had sex? -Yeah, consensual.
那很粗暴，但都是她要求的
It was rough, but she was screaming for it.
第二天早上，我家门口来了两个条子
Next morning, there's two cops at my door.
艾米有与强奸一致的伤痕
Amy has wounds that are consistent with rape.
手腕上有绷带的痕迹，还有我的精液
Ligature marks on her wrist, and my semen.
看起来就像我把艾米绑了起来然后强奸了她
It looks like I've tied Amy to my bed, and raped her.
我！
Me!
之后，你猜他们找到了什么
And then, guess what they find.
床头两边
Headboards of my bed, one on each side.
你不会戴的那种领带
the ties you wouldn't wear
你真了解你妻子
You do know your wife.
-你后来再见过她吗 -有
-Did you ever see her again? -Yeah.
电视上，就上周，和你一起
On TV, last week, with you.
我想，“艾米又来了
I thought, "there's Amy.
“她已经从被强奸进化到被谋杀了”
"She's graduated from being raped to being murdered."
你也一直在看这个是吗？
You been watching this, too?
昨晚的的爆炸
Last night's bombshell.
新闻
We just found out...
艾米艾略特，事实上她失踪时已经怀孕了
Amy elliott dunne was, indeed, pregnant when she went missing.
凯里卡皮托诺，这真的让我恶心
Kelly capitono, this makes me wanna throw up.
是什么让一个怀孕的女人，一个怀有生命的女人
What is it about a pregnant woman, a woman carrying life inside her...
把一个男人变成禽兽
That turns men into animals?
艾伦，这不是个例
Ellen, this is an epidemic.
怀孕女性死亡的第三个主要原因
The third leading cause of death among pregnant women...
就是被男友和丈夫杀害
Is homicide committed by a boyfriend or husband.
让我们铭记她
Let's not forget about the wife, ever.
今晚，我们欢迎艾米最好的朋友，诺艾尔霍桑
Tonight, we welcome Amy's best friend, noelle hawthorne.
谢谢你接受采访
Thanks for being on the show, noelle.
谢谢，艾伦
Thank you, Ellen.
让我先说一句
And let me just say this...
艾米如果活着一定会感谢你的，还有你对女人们做的一切
Amy would have loved you, and all you do for women.
噢，你过奖了
Oh, that's nice.
为什么不跟我们谈谈你的朋友呢？诺艾尔
Why don't you tell us about your friend, noelle?
艾米很有母爱
Amy was so nurturing.
噢，我倒希望有人，就算就一次
Oh, I'd love if just once, someone was like...
“她是个贱货”
"She was a real rag."
她美丽，聪明，友善
She was beautiful and smart and kind.
我觉得她就是个死婊子
Seems like a rich bitch to me.
你什么意思，人们爱她啊？
What do you mean? People love her.
我不知道，她看起来好傲慢、易失控
I don't know. She seems uppity.
一个惯坏的富有女孩，嫁给了一个骗人的混账。
Spoiled rich girl,married a cheating asshole.
最终自食其果
Paid the ultimate price.
唯一的秘密就是她的丈夫，我们从未见过尼克
The only secret was her husband. We never met Nick.
他从来不介绍他自己
He never introduced himself.
为什么这样呢，诺艾尔？你怎么考虑呢？
Why was that, noelle? Why do you think?
我觉得我们都知道为什么
I think we know why.
因为他有粗暴脾气
Because he had a violent temper.
有一些残酷是吧
A little harsh.
这就是人生，宝贝
That's life, baby.
他早知道我早就看穿他了
He knew I'd have seen right through him.
别误解我的意图、看错我
Don't get me wrong.
我没有说他杀她是说得过去的
I'm not saying it's okay he killed her.
我只是在说，世上总是有因果
I'm just saying, there are consequences.
艹，对
Fuck, yeah.
她多孤独啊！
She was so alone.
而且她是多么无辜
And she was so innocent.
你是个好朋友，诺艾尔，而且你也是我们节目的好友。
You're a good friend, noelle. And you're a good friend of the show.
谢谢你的参与
Thanks for coming on.
请告诉我你把坦纳博尔特谈妥了
Please tell me you landed Tanner bolt.
坦纳.博尔特搞定我了
Tanner bolt landed me.
回去路上我会想法见见德西.科林斯斯
I'm gonna try and see desi collings on my way home.
还有 格...
And, go...
坦纳要十万定金
Tanner's retainer is $100,000.
而且只是定金
That's just the retainer.
听着，我有47，000美元作为存款，我个人退休账户还有2500美元
Listen, I've got $47,000 in savings. I've got $2,500 in an ira.
我接受再次抵押房产，我们以此为战
I'm approved for a second mortgage on the house. We will go from there.
谢谢你
Thank you.
-我爱你 -我也爱你
-I love you. -I love you, too.
尼克把有老年痴呆的父亲放在养老院里
Nick keeps his father, who has Alzheimer's, in a facility.
每年他拜访几次？一次
Number of times he visited last year? One.
我艹！
Oh, fuck!
他的双胞胎妹妹玛戈，她么，是个桃色“极品”
His twin sister, margo, well, she is a peach.
他们在艾米给他们买的酒吧里度日
These two spend their days in the bar Amy bought them.
搞什么？劳伦，炒房子？
Playing what, Lauren? Playing house?
什么鬼
What the fuck?
双胞胎兄妹总会黏糊在一块互相挑逗
Twin siblings often enable and abet.
虽然我从未检察过尼克或者是他妹妹...
While I never examined Nick, or his sister...
他们俩似乎非常非常亲密
They both seem very, very close.
这是双胞胎乱伦
It's twin-cest.
令人作呕地亲近，劳伦
Disturbingly close, Lauren.
这样，让我们以一个问题做结尾
And so, we close with a question.
是什么样的道德腐朽...
What kind of moral rot...
让一个美丽、富有天分、和蔼、聪颖富有爱心的母亲...
Allows a beautiful, talented, kind, smart, loving mother...
在上天没有听到我们愤慨的呼号下消失
To vanish without the heavens hearing our outraged cries?
我能抽支烟么？
Can I bum a cigarette?
艾米艾略特道恩,我们在乎你，我们不会忘记
Amy elliott dunne, we care about you, and we will not forget.
你知道我们还不会忘记什么吗？
And you know what else we won't forget?
密苏里州有死刑
Missouri has the death penalty.
阿门
Amen.
我想报告一些奇怪的行为
I'd like to report some strange activity...
在一个属于玛格.道恩财产的木屋的附近
Near the woodshed on the property of one margo dunne.
嗨
Hey.
-道恩先生 -科林斯斯先生
-Mr. dunne. -Mr. collings.
我认识你 在志愿中心见过
I know you. I saw you at the volunteer center.
我想帮助
I wanted to help.
希望你不要介意我的来访
I hope you don't mind me coming by.
我从这封你写给我妻子的信中得知你的地址
I got your address from this letter that you wrote my wife.
艾米和我信仰已经流失的写信的艺术
Amy and I believe in the lost art of letter-writing.
我一直很好奇 你和她之间消逝了那么多往事
I always wondered why you kept in touch after...
为何还联系彼此
Everything.
你们在寄宿学校谈过两年恋爱 对吗
You were together for two years in boarding school, right?
她是我的第一个真正的女友
She was my first serious girlfriend.
-你们为何分手了 -这是个奇怪的问题
-Why did you break up? -That's a strange question.
你待她不好吗 还是对她不忠
Did you treat her bad? Did you cheat on her?
这是个粗鲁的问题
That's a rude question.
我来告诉你艾米是怎么说的
Let me tell you what Amy told me.
她甩了你 你整个人魂飞魄散
She dumped you, you completely unraveled.
跟踪她 威胁她
You stalked her, you threatened her...
还试图在她床上自杀 后来被送去治疗
And you attempted suicide in her bed and were institutionalized.
你的妻子失踪了，你就千里迢迢来告诉我这些？
Your wife is missing, and you came all this way to tell me this?
我原以为会听到这故事的另一个版本
I thought there might be another side to this story.
科林斯斯先生
Mr. collings.
艹
Fuck.
...有关艾米艾略特道恩的失踪案件
...the missing persons case of Amy elliott dunne.
她是惊异孩童艾米少儿书籍系列的那位美丽的金发碧眼的书籍作家
She is the beautiful blonde inspiration for the amazing Amy kids' book series.
你又在读那个日记？
You're reading that diary again?
你知道它是怎么结束的
You know how it ends.
这令我感兴趣
It interests me.
嗨，朗达
Hey, Rhonda.
“他会杀了我。”——完
"He's gonna kill me." The end.
为什么他要去他爸爸家，去烧掉它？
Why did he go to his dad's house to burn it?
那里是私人场所，没有人在那里
It's private. There's no one there.
为什么他不确保它已经烧完？
Why didn't he make sure it actually burned?
因为他触碰了警报，你打着手电筒紧撵着他
Because he tripped the alarm. You were up his ass with a flashlight.
整个事情就让人觉得离奇
The whole thing just feels hinky.
就比如说找见一个写着“线索”的信封
Like finding an envelope marked "clue."
你听过那个说法么？
You ever hear the expression...
最简单的答案往往是正确的
"The simplest answer is often the correct one"?
实际上，我从来不觉得那是正确的
Actually, I've never found that to be true.
-晚安 -晚安
-Good night. -Good night.
埃尔维斯来密苏里州了
Elvis is in Missouri.
感谢上帝，进来吧
Thank God. Come on in.
关于艾米你需要知道的第一件事是 她喜欢教训人
First thing you have to understand about Amy, she loves to teach lessons.
-扮演上帝 -对 旧约里的
-Play God.-Yeah, old testament God.
好的，继续说
Okay. Keep talking.
她发现我背着她搞上了安迪
She finds out I've been cheating on her with Andie...
决定给我点教训
Decides to teach me a lesson.
伪造她自己的死亡 嫁祸给我
Fakes her own death, frames me for it.
房里的血迹 信用卡 人寿保险
Blood in the house, credit cards, life insurance.
她发起的寻宝游戏
She does the treasure hunt.
现在寻宝游戏至关重要
Now, the treasure hunt is critical.
她安排了一场游历我不忠之路的旅行 遍览我的罪状
She's taking us on a tour of my infidelities. Rubbing my nose in it.
她还给警察留下了线索一
And she leaves clue number one for the police...
它会引导他们找到我的办公室
Which will lead them back to my office...
我和安迪时常在那里...
Which is a place where Andie and I would often...
她故意留下了一条红内裤
And she leaves a pair of red panties.
对的，蕾茜，看起来糟糕
Right. Racy, looks bad.
-线索二呢 -我爸的房子
-Clue two. -My father's house.
另一个安迪和我偶尔幽会的地点
Another place where Andie and I would occasionally have relations.
-线索三呢 -小木屋
-Clue three? -Woodshed.
-也是幽会的...  -我的天哪
-Also a location... -Oh, my God.
-我们无处可去 -旅馆开房啊
-We had limited options. -A hotel.
-艾米会发现我用了信用卡支付 -那用安迪的信用卡呀
-Amy would have seen the credit card bill.-Put it on Andie's credit card.
安迪的是和她父母绑在一起的
Andie's statement went right to her parents.
尼克，玛戈我们能到小棕屋去看看么？
Nick, margo, can we head over to the little brown house?
-这线索指向什么 -我爸的房子
-This leads us to what? -My dad's house.
老爸房子是蓝的
Dad's house is blue.
爸妈离婚后 当他不在我们身边时
After the divorce,when dad wasn't coming around...
我常假装他是一个名为brown先生的间谍
I used to pretend that he was a spy named Mr. brown, who...
为了孩子们的安全 必须否认他们的存在
For the sake of his children's safety, had to deny their existence.
你从来没有告诉过我这些
You never told me that.
你告诉她这些？
You told her that?
我们在你的办公室找到了证明你有罪的红裤衩
We've got incriminating red panties in your office.
我们在你的小木屋里拿到了价值好比博物馆展厅大开放的一大摊子玩意儿
We've got a showcase showdown worth of crap in your woodshed.
所以，以上帝之名在你的父亲的房子里究竟有什么，尼克？
So, what in God's name is at your father's house, Nick?
说实话
And be honest.
我真的不知道
I honestly have no idea.
无论他们找到了什么，我觉得最好假设这东西非常不糟糕
Whatever they found, I think it's safe to assume that it's very bad.
不可控因素太多了
We got a lot of uncontained issues here.
尼克，你对于安蒂的内心想法有任何了解吗？
Nick, do you have any idea as to what Andie's mindset is?
自从守夜后我们就没交流过
We haven't communicated since the vigil.
好吧，艾米的父母呢？
Okay. Amy's parents?
-没 就是...  -压力更大了
-No, it's... -More pressure.
我们有个硬伤，你的这个年轻的女友毫无疑问会在任何时间公开发言
We got a hurt, young girlfriend who will no doubt go public at any moment.
-不 安迪不会那样做的  -她会的
-No, Andie won't do that. -She will.
他们总是这样，这件事，不能太针对她
They always do. Don't take it personally.
艾米把我们困在了一个十分有趣的窘境中
Amy's got us in an interesting bind.
我们要告诉警察有关安蒂的事情 - 真的么？
-We need to tell the cops about Andie. -Really?
现在，安蒂又给你提供了一个动机
Right now, Andie just gives you another motive.
我们要告诉警察有关木屋的事情
We need to tell the cops about the woodshed.
我们要占有这两件事的先机
We need to be on the front end of that.
但是我要警告你将要发生的事
But I'm gonna warn you as to what will happen.
他们会抓玛格
They'll go after margo.
他们能这么做吗 不能吧
They can't do that, can they?
她是你的从犯，她帮助你藏匿证据
She's your accomplice. She helped you hide the evidence.
在所有估计中，都指向她知道你杀了艾米
In all likelihood, she knows that you killed Amy.
那我们接下来怎么做？
Well, what are we going to do?
我们找到艾米
We find Amy.
不，其它策略都是不着要点的
No. Any other strategy is missing the point.
我有两个前机密服务人员，他们很有能耐
I've got two ex-secret service guys that are really good.
我会把他们放到这件事上
I'll put them on it.
但是他们从哪里开始呢，尼克？
But where do they start, Nick?
艾米可能去哪里？
Where would Amy go?
我真的一头雾水
I have no idea.
我们在算分数么？
Are we keeping score?
嘿！
Hey!
我还以为游戏中我们在这一会儿排除男人
I thought we were steering clear of men for a while.
他很不错
He's nice.
因为他想干你
Because he wants to fuck you.
她还对她的前夫耿耿于怀么？
She's still moping about her ex?
他也被别人戴过绿帽子
He got cheated on, too.
我们三个是在奥扎克地区最难过的被踹的
We three are the saddest sacks in all the ozarks.
我不难过
I'm not sad.
我愤怒
I'm angry.
走你
There you go.
我险些喝酒喝到死，当我的妻子离开我的时候
I almost drank myself to death when my wife left me.
我要自杀，你能相信么？
I was gonna kill myself. Can you believe that?
不要给他这样的美事
Don't give him the pleasure.
我想把我淹死在墨西哥湾
I was going to drown myself in the Gulf of Mexico...
让我做大白鲨的晚餐
Let myself be dinner for the great whites.
湾里面都是牛头鲨，诺琳斯小姐
Gulf is bull sharks, miss nawlins.
我为什么要死，我又不是混蛋
Why should I die? I'm not the asshole.
把那个写到T恤上吧
Please put that on a t-shirt.
钱包女士，我还以为你说你破产了
Miss moneybags. I thought you said you were broke.
那可是很肥一卷
That's a fat wad.
主要是零票
It's mostly singles.
零钱？你是什么，脱衣舞娘？
Singles? What are you, a stripper?
沉沦的女子，还是财宝箱？
Swamp girls, or treasure chest?
我们只是开玩笑
We're just teasing.
诺拉那里人们不是爱开玩笑么？
Don't they tease people down in nola?
我们现在任何时候都可以把尼克道恩逮捕
We can expect Nick dunne's arrest any day now.
我们在房子里面找到了血迹，大笔债款和不想要的怀孕
We've got blood in the house, huge debt, an unwanted pregnancy.
我们还有已经失踪5天的艾米
And we have Amy elliott dunne,missing for five days...
为正义而呼号
Crying out for justice.
我们马上回来
We'll be right back.
坦纳有个很不好的主意，他打算把你抛到公众眼下
Tanner has a very bad idea he's going to pitch you.
是吗
Yeah?
你要明天再圣路易斯参与莎朗席贝尔节目
You're doing Sharon schieber tomorrow in St. Louis.
这可能会坏了事
It could go so wrong.
你还要告诉她有关安蒂的事情
And you are going to tell her about Andie.
休想
Nope.
听起来不是个好主意
That sounds like a very bad idea.
你已经三天没有她的消息了
You haven't heard from her in three days.
这是个在嘀嗒作响的定时炸弹，你必须接受这事
This is a ticking time bomb. You've gotta throw yourself on it.
-人们会憎恨我的 -然后他们才能原谅你
-People are gonna hate me. -And then, they will forgive you.
一个人在电视上承认自己是个混蛋？
A guy admitting that he's a gigantic asshole on television?
人们会同情的
People empathize with that.
-干嘛不直接发个声明 -他们需要亲眼看见你
-Why don't we just put out a statement? -They need to see you.
莎朗的特殊节目，有一千万观众
Sharon's specials, they get 10 million viewers.
她是一架巡洋舰，如果她把你作为一个信息源、动力
She is a crusader. If she takes you on as a cause
她会问一些很致命的问题
she's going to ask real questions.
我会像为宣誓作词一样训练你
I will drill you as if you were doing a deposition.
该说什么，不该说什么
What to say, what not to say.
一个训练有素的猴子？
A trained monkey?
一个不会接受致命神经注射（死刑）的训练有素的猴子
A trained monkey who doesn't get the lethal injection.
尼克，这事有关人们对你的想法
Nick, this case is about what people think of you.
我们需要他们喜欢你
They need to like you.
现在，你做这件事，你就能接触到百万个这样的人
Now, you do this and you will reach millions of those people.
或许只要一个就行了
Maybe I only need to reach one.
你好？
Hello?
嗨，宝贝
Hey, baby.
等等
One minute.
嗨 -嗨
-Hey. -Hey.
你要走收拾收拾走么？
You clearing out?
不，我只是清扫清扫
No, I'm just cleaning up.
让我们来说再见吧
Let us come in and say goodbye.
我会在...之前回来看你们
I'll come by before--
让我们帮帮你
let us give you a hand.
是啊，你要扫清这里所有的东西
Yeah, you gotta clear everything out, here.
多罗茜是个很讲究的人
Dorothy is a real stickler.
你连一个多余的挂钩都不留下
Not even a spare hanger can you leave behind.
得确保没有一点东西裹在里面
Gotta make sure nothing's tucked inside.
一个袜子...
A sock...
或者是内裤或者你是不是留下了...
Or undies or what have you.
你干的很不错啊
You did a real good job.
钱呢，甜心？
Where is the money, sweetheart?
看看她衣服下面
Look under her dress.
他劝你这么做的？
He talked you into this?
我劝他这么做的
I talked him into it.
你们一走，我就叫条子
The second you leave, I'm calling the cops.
你的眼镜是假的，你的头发染得乱乱的
Your glasses are fake. Your hair's dyed all hamster.
你说你叫南希，但是叫你时，甚至一半时间都不答应这个名字
You say your name's Nancy, but you don't even answer to it half the time.
你在躲着，我不知道为什么，我也不太在意
You're hiding. I don't know why, and I don't really care.
但是你不会叫条子
But you ain't gonna call the cops.
而且我也不觉得你曾经真的挨过打
And I don't think you've ever really been hit before.
艹他娘的
Holy shit.
对不起，但是我们真的需要钱
Sorry, but we really need the money.
下次，更小心一点，好么？
Next place, be more careful, okay?
在外面还有好多人比我们还要坏
There are a lot of people out there a lot worse than we are.
打扰了，你不能在这里睡
Excuse me. You can't sleep here.
我没有杀害我妻子
I did not kill my wife.
你为什么不再试试？有点木
Why don't you try it again? A little less wooden.
我没有杀我的妻子
I didn't kill my wife.
-你这是干嘛 -每当你看着自命不凡时...
-What are you doing? -Every time you look smug...
或者是不满或者是紧张，我就用一个胶糖小熊砸你
Or annoyed or tense, I'm gonna hit you with a gummy bear.
-这样我就不紧张了吗 -我们再试试
-That's supposed to make me less tense? -Let's try it again.
道恩先生，从我所了解到，你和你的老婆有些摩擦
Mr. dunne, from what I understand, you and your wife had some bumps.
没错，我们过了几年苦日子，我失业了
Yeah, we had some tough years. I lost my job.
你们都丢了
You both did.
我们俩都失业了
We both lost our jobs.
为了照料我母亲 我们必须搬回密苏里
I had to move back home so we could take care of my mother...
她患了乳腺癌 而我父亲 他
Who was dying of cancer and my dad, who had--
你爸爸是个呆瓜
your dad's scorched earth.
让我们谈谈你的母亲，你们之间有多亲密
Let's talk about your mom, how close you were.
继续
Go on.
有一段时间 情况有所好转
For a while, things had been building up.
“积聚起来”暗示着一场爆炸将要发生，不行
"Built up" implies that an explosion is coming. No.
某个层面来说 我们走入了歧途
At a certain point, we got on the wrong track.
我一时变得懦弱
I had a moment of weakness.
你的“一刻”超过了15个月
Your "moment" was over 15 months.
我对我妻子不敬
I disrespected my wife.
也辜负了美好的婚姻
And I disrespected my marriage.
我会后悔一辈子
And I'll always regret it.
就这样
That works.
不要害怕装起一副丈夫的样子
Don't be afraid to play up the dufus husband thing, Nick.
我是个傻瓜，我是个混蛋
"I was an idiot. I'm a fuck-up.
“我做错了所有事”
"Everything I do is wrong."
我懂 就是男人那些傻逼德行
I know. What men are supposed to do in general.
-谢谢 -感觉如何
-Thank you. -How do you feel?
感觉良好 格 把那个盒子递给我好吗
I feel good. Go, can you pass me that box, please?
这是艾米给我的三十三岁生日礼物
It's Amy's 33rd birthday present to me.
你恨那块表
You hate that watch.
哪有 格 我爱死那块表了
No, go. I love that watch.
就想我爱这幅领带一样
Just like I love this tie.
就想我爱我的妻子一样
Just like I love my wife.
是你！
It's you!
是你
It's you.
对不起
I'm sorry.
感谢上苍
Good God.
上周...
Last week...
我威胁要离开，然后他说他会找到我而且要杀了我
I threatened to leave, and he said he'd find me and he'd kill me.
所以，我消失了
So, I disappeared.
我失去了孩子
I lost the baby.
我不能告诉我的家长
I couldn't even tell my parents.
我感到很羞耻而且我很害怕
I'm so ashamed and I'm so afraid.
这么说，他在找你
Well, he is looking for you.
他三天前出现在我的门前
He showed up on my doorstep three days ago.
他从我给你的信中追踪到了我
He tracked me from my letters to you.
你保存了它们
You saved them.
知道你还在...
Knowing you were out there...
是唯一让我在过去的几年中坚持下来的东西
Was the only thing that's kept me going these past few years.
咱们找警察，你可以解释一切
Let's go to the police.You can explain everything.
不，我现在不可以现身
No, I can't turn up now.
我会像贱民一样，每个人都会恨我
I'd be a pariah. Everyone would hate me.
让尼克坐牢是错的么？
Is it wrong to want Nick to go to prison?
他就该为他所做进牢
He should go to prison for what he's done.
我会把你安置在我的湖边的房子中
I'm setting you up at my lake house.
它彻底与外界隔绝
It's utterly secluded.
你为什么对我这么好
Why are you so good to me?
你知道为什么
You know why.
打扰一下
Excuse me.
我知道你，不是么？
I know you, don't I?
不
No.
你是来自诺兰的女孩，不是么？
You're one of the nolan girls, right?
不，我们来自维尼皮厄，我们也打扰了
No, we're from winnipeg. Excuse us.
我们应该走
We should leave.
等等
Just a second.
是伯尼的电话，我一会给她打电话
That was boney. I'll call her later.
坦纳，很高兴见到你
Tanner. Nice to see you.
莎朗,嗨！
Sharon! Hi.
但愿这事值得我的时间
Hope this is worth my while.
你会很高兴的
You're gonna be very happy.
莎朗你好
Sharon.
席贝尔女士，很感谢你做这些
Ms. schieber. Thank you so much for doing this.
我能在我们开始之前招待一下你的吃喝么？
Can I get you anything to drink or eat before we get started?
什么鬼？
What the fuck?
抱歉？
I'm sorry?
现在我们有关惊奇艾米失踪案有一个重大的进展
We have a major shocking development in the amazing Amy disappearance.
我们现在直播这个故事
We go live to that story now.
哦，我的天
Oh, my God.
你个小贱货
You little slut.
我的名字是安蒂菲茨杰拉德
My name is Andie Fitzgerald.
我遇到了尼古拉斯道恩...
I met Nicholas dunne...
在磨坊山谷中，他是我的启蒙写作老师时
When he was my creative writing teacher at mill valley.
为什么她穿着像一个保姆一样
Why is she dressed like a babysitter?
我感到深深的羞愧...
I am deeply ashamed...
有关和一个已婚男子不切实地浪漫地纠缠在一起
Of having been romantically involved with a married man.
那个有巨大的诱人抚舐的奶头的女的
The girl with the giant cum-on-me tits.
我真心认为我们相爱了
I truly believed we were in love.
现在，她看起来就他娘的像门诺派教徒一样
Now, she looks like a fucking mennonite.
我知道这不是理由
I know that is no excuse.
不，确实这不是
No, it is not.
在我心中，我不认为尼克道恩会为了我而杀人
I do not, in my heart, believe Nick dunne would have killed for me.
我的祈祷飘向每一个爱艾米的人
My prayers go out to everyone who loves Amy.
我为这件事给他们带来的痛苦道歉
I apologize for the pain this has caused them.
我们曾经爱尼克道恩就像爱儿子一样
We have loved Nick dunne like a son.
如今，这份爱停止了
That love ended today.
来吧，你在盯着鬼看呢
Come on, you're staring at ghosts.
他用谎言一次又一次回应我们的信任
He met our trust with lie after lie.
我们现在可以确凿地认为
We now absolutely believe...
尼克与我们女儿的失踪有紧密的关系
Nick is involved in the disappearance of our daughter.
我们的超凡艾米
Our amazing Amy.
这才变得非常令人兴奋起来
This just got very exciting.
我们需要一点时间
We need a moment.
我们要立刻撤出这个节目
We're gonna have to bow out of this.
-一切都没变啊 -已经天翻地覆了
-Nothing has changed. -Everything has changed.
一个小时之前，我们占有这件事的先机，现在呢？
An hour ago, we were ahead of this. Now?
-我能搞定的 -现在我们是防守方
-I can handle this. -We're on the defense.
这是完全不同的状态了
This is a completely different dynamic.
我能应付这事 -她会把你活活干掉，难为死你的
-I can handle it. -She's going to eat you alive.
相信我
Just trust me.
好吧
Okay.
好
Great.
给他戴上麦克风
Mic him.
一，二，三，四，五
One, two, three, four, five.
谢谢
Thank you.
他不该对化妆师笑
He shouldn't smile at the makeup artist.
是啊，这可不是玩闹
Yeah, no kidding.
开始录制，五...四...
Roll tape. Five... four...
三...二...
Three... two...
说真的，我不敢相信你他妈有这么棒
Seriously, I can't believe how fucking good you were.
-多亏艾米擢升我咯 -别来
-Amy brings out the best in me. -Don't.
你们俩这事情要收敛、不要声张，至少在接下来的24小时内
Keep it together, you two. At least for the next 24 hours.
人们依然恨你们，女人想抠出你们的眼睛
People still hate you. Women want to scratch your eyes out.
安蒂在电视上很不错
Andie was really good TV.
-她是个好女孩 -问题正在于此
-She's a good person. -Therein lies the problem.
挺过这一阵子...
Ride this out...
当莎朗节目明天播放时，我们就会看到一个全新的你
And when Sharon airs tomorrow, we'll be looking at a whole new you.
但是在那之前...
But, until then...
别露脸
Don't show your face.
没问题
No problem.
欢迎
Welcome.
请自便
Make yourself at home.
我这里有音乐，卫星电视
I've got music, satellite...
网飞、罗库：都是美国网络电视提供商
网飞
Netflix.
他本是她的老师
He was her teacher!
罗库
Roku.
当然有网络
Internet, obviously.
他本是一个应该早已成熟的男人
Here is a supposedly grown man--
如果有任何很喜欢却找不到的东西
if there is ever anything you have a taste for and you can't find it...
就让我知道，我会给你找到
Just let me know and I will get it for you.
不教写作的常识，他却教会了她勾引男人
Instead of the a-b-c's, he taught her the birds and the bees.
而且再想想她母亲在这时候会有什么感受
And just think how her mother must feel at a time like this.
酒窖就在楼下
Wine cellar's downstairs.
我也会给你找一些衣服
I'll get you some clothes, too.
反正我早已不欣赏勾引男人的吧台小姐
Not that I don't appreciate bait shop chic.
有地热，就像你喜欢的那样
The floors are heated, just dial to your liking.
这里还有浴袍和毛巾，淋浴室有桑拿房
There's robes and towels. The shower has steam.
浴缸有按摩功能
The bathtub has a massage cycle.
假如你还有心思的话，这里景色非常好
There's a great view, if you're in the mood.
如果没有心思，遮开窗帘
Blackout curtains if you're not.
床很宽
The bed is savoir.
你不会睡得比这还好
You'll never get a better sleep.
这就是我要的
This is just what I need.
我太疲惫了
I'm so exhausted.
那我就把这里交给你了
I'll leave you to it, then.
艾米，我真高兴你在这里
Amy, I am so happy that you are here.
而且我不想让你担心，一刻都不要
And I don't want you to worry for one moment.
这里到处都是摄像头
There are cameras everywhere.
外部，一直到地面，入口
The exterior, all along the grounds, the entryway.
任何人...
Anyone...
被发现来或是离开
Who is caught coming or going...
都会被记录下来
Will be recorded.
你非常安全
You are more than safe.
而且我再也不会让你离开了
And I am not letting you get away again.
早上好！-别这么做
-Good morning! -Don't do that!
对不起
I'm sorry.
我需要感到安全
I need to feel safe.
你非常安全
You are very safe.
你在忙什么？ -没什么
-What have you been up to? -Nothing.
艾米，我不是尼克
Amy, I'm not Nick.
这对我来说很难
It's hard for me.
这么多年过去了，在某人的掌控之下
After so many years under someone's thumb...
我完全了解这事什么感受
I know just what that feels like.
你从来都没有在我的掌控之下过
You were never under my thumb.
被你限制过 -从没有 -
-On your leash. -Never.
一个新的开始
A new start.
优良的衣服
Decent clothes.
染发剂，化妆品，镊子
Hair dye. Makeup. Tweezers.
迎着湖的上面有一个健身房
There's a gym overlooking the lake.
你越快看起来像自己，你越快感觉像自己
The sooner you look like yourself, the sooner you'll feel like yourself.
我会买上今晚的蔬菜，咱们会看莎朗的节目，并且最终继续生活
I'll get groceries for tonight, we'll watch Sharon schieber, and finally move on.
我觉得这是应该让我自己看的节目
I think that's something I should watch on my own.
胡说
Nonsense.
我会回来的
I'll be back.
而且我正在期待...
And I am looking forward...
和艾米艾略特的复合
To my reunion with Amy elliott.
真棒
Great.
晚上好，我是莎朗席蓓尔
Good evening, I'm Sharon schieber.
今晚，独家专有... -快来
-Tonight, exclusively...-Hurry up.
一名丈夫打破他的沉默，不仅仅只是有关他妻子的失踪
A husband breaks his silence, not just on his wife's disappearance...
而是讲述他自己的亵婚行为以及所有这些令人震惊的流言
But on his infidelity, and all those shocking rumors.
尼克道恩
Nick dunne...
你大概是美国现在最痛恨的人了
You're probably the most hated man in America right now.
或许吧 也许我是罪有应得
I probably am. And I probably deserve it.
我买的那个领带
I bought that tie.
你杀了你的妻子么，尼克？
Did you kill your wife, Nick?
我没有杀害我妻子
I did not kill my wife.
我不是谋杀犯
I am not a murderer.
但你不忠
But you were unfaithful.
我确实出轨了
I was unfaithful.
我还羞愧难当
And I am deeply ashamed.
而且，以这些为前提，你要让艾米的父母...
And, on top of that, you allowed Amy's parents...
她的朋友，所有这些在你家乡的人...
Her friends, all the people in your hometown...
相信你是一位有爱心的，极度渴望得想找到所失踪的妻子的丈夫？
Believe you were a loving husband, desperate to find his missing wife.
我的确是不顾一切想要找到我妻子
Well, I am desperate to find my missing wife.
你这么说，但是我很奇怪你大概是怎么希望我们相信你
You say that, but I'm wondering how you expect us to believe you...
如今我们知道你是个骗子
Now that we know you're a liar.
我之前没有承认自己的外遇
I didn't come forward with my affair...
因为我知道那会令我的形象彻底毁掉
Because I knew it would make me look really, really bad.
但我再也不在意那些了
But I don't care about that anymore.
我只想找到我的妻子
I just want to find my wife.
-我只想搞清楚 -让我给你说清楚吧
-I am just trying to be clear... -Let me be clear
我虽不是谋杀犯 但我也的确不是个好人
Just because I am not a murderer doesn't make me a good guy.
我不是一个好人
I'm not a good guy.
我是一位好妻子的坏丈夫
I was a bad husband to a great wife.
我违背了对她的誓言
I broke the vow that I made to her
这些都是漂亮话啊，尼克
Those are pretty words, Nick.
但是这些究竟在你而言有什么内涵呢？
But what does that really mean to you?
总之 我是个大骗子
It basically means that I was a con artist.
我七年前遇见了艾米.艾略特
I met Amy elliott seven years ago.
对她一见钟情
I was completely transfixed.
艾米对你有这么大影响？
Amy can do that to you.
我是从平凡地方来的平凡小伙
I was this average guy from an average place...
没什么远大抱负
With mediocre aspirations.
而我遇到了一个让我目眩神迷的女人
And I met a woman who dazzled me.
我想要她爱我
And I wanted her to love me...
所以我佯装自己是一个更加出色的男人
So I pretended to be better than I was.
当我们结婚时 我允诺我会成为那种男人
When we got married, I promised to be that guy.
他会勤奋工作
That guy who works harder.
他会精彩地生活
That guy who, who lives and acts...
并且像她一样竭尽全力去爱
And loves with as much passion as she does.
但我辜负了她
But I failed her.
我没有做出正确的举措
Instead of doing what was right...
我选择懦弱与逃避
I did what was easy.
你说这话就像一个相信可以对自己的妻子做补偿的男人
You talk like a man who believes he can make amends to his wife.
一个相信自己妻子还活着的男人
Who believes his wife is still alive.
她一定还活着
She is still alive.
你能为我看着这个相机么？
Will you look at that camera for me?
你愿意看着镜头
Will you look in the lens...
对你妻子说句话吗？
And talk to your wife?
如果她在外面，今晚能看到、听到你
If she is out there, able to hear and see you tonight...
你想对她说什么，尼克？
What would you like to say to her, Nick?
艾米 我爱你
Amy, I love you.
你是我见过的最好的人
You're the best person I've ever known.
我对自己卑劣的作为感到无比后悔
And I've taken myself to the woodshed for the way that I've treated you.
如果你回来 我保证
And if you come back, I promise...
我会用余生的每一天来补偿你
I will spend every day making it up to you.
我会成为我曾经许诺成为的那个人
I will be the man that I promised you I would be.
我爱你
I love you.
回家吧
Come home.
给我吧
Here.
不论你怎么想
Regardless of what you thought...
怎么样
What does it say?
我想我们一致认为
...I think we can all agree...
噢，我的天啊，你他妈成功了
Oh, my God. You fucking killed it.
事情并非想象的那样
...there's more to him than meets the eye.
他们都为你疯狂了
They're going crazy for you.
他们从不喜欢我 喜欢我 恨我
They disliked me, they liked me, they hated me.
到现在的爱我
And now they love me.
坦诚的人值得敬重
...a candor and an honesty that's worthy of respect.
显然他赢得了我的尊重
He's certainly earned mine.
什么？
What is it?
我是莎伦席蓓尔，晚上好
I'm Sharon schieber. Good night.
玛戈道恩，这是对你住宅进行搜查的许可证
Margo dunne, this is a search warrant for your property.
我一般不会在意提供线索的电话
I usually ignore tipline calls...
不过有个邻居担心有个可疑的家伙出现在柴房附近
But a neighbor was concerned about a strange man around your woodshed.
打给坦纳
Call Tanner.
好的，艹
Okay. Fuck!
你女朋友真是可爱，尼克
Girlfriend's real cute, Nick.
这就是你来的目的吗
Is that what this is about?
整个调查期间我对你太客气了
I have treated you more than fair  throughout this entire investigation.
我一次又一次不无端怀疑你
I gave you the benefit of the doubt over and over.
每次你说一些蠢话
Every time you said something stupid...
我都想，也许他就是蠢
I thought, "maybe he's just stupid."
但我错了，这就是原因
But I was wrong. That's what this is about.
这些球杆是你打高尔夫的吗？
Are these the clubs you don't play golf with?
没有一个是我的
None of that is mine.
没有一个是我摆在那里的
None of this was put here by me.
这些都是很好的球杆，你把这变成了男人的巢穴
Those are nice clubs. You got the makings of a real man cave.
所有一切好东西都等着妻子消失
Everything just waiting until the wife goes away for good.
尼克！
Nick!
-你不能这样做 -我们当然可以
-You can't do that! -Of course we can.
艾米，是时候往前看了
Amy, it's time to move on.
我能怎么帮助你？
What can I do to help?
我需要一些思考的时间
I need some time to think.
那是你最不需要的 -德西
-That's the last thing you need. -Desi--
20年，你一直吊着我
twenty years, you have kept me dangling.
最后，在昨晚，你来找我，你选择了我
Finally, last night, you came to me, and you chose me.
相信自己的直觉吧
Follow that instinct.
不要相信致使你被毒打和无家可归的直觉
Don't trust the instinct that left you beaten and homeless...
谁在车上，在恐惧中生活
Sleeping in your car, fearing for your life.
我不会强求
I'm not gonna force myself on you.
你说的我都知道
I understand what you're saying, desi.
我知道
I do.
只是我被虐待了那么长时间
I've been so mistreated for so long.
我已经忘记该怎么办
I've forgotten how to behave.
我明天就回搬过来
I'll move in here tomorrow...
我们可以一起想办法
And we'll work it out together.
我只希望你做你自己
I just want you to be you again.
他们抓了玛格是为了吓唬你
They only took margo to fuck with you.
她不能在那里再多待他妈的一秒
She's not spending another fucking second in there.
我要走进去 然后告诉他们真相
I'm gonna go in, and I'm gonna tell them everything.
怎么了
What?
我们只能给邦尼透露一点
We tell boney very little.
没有尸体，没有凶器
Without a body, without a murder weapon...
他们唯一的希望就是你认罪
Their only hope is a confession.
所以，你让他们去说
So, you let them do all the talking.
那样，我们可以随时调整辩词
That way, we can jump-start your defense.
真相就是我的辩词
The truth is my defense.
认得这些吗？
Recognize these?
是的 艾米送我的周年纪念礼物
Yes. It's Amy's anniversary present to me.
她是在告诉你她怀孕了是吗，尼克？
Was that how she told you she was pregnant, Nick?
妈咪，爸爸，孩子，这让你和生气吗？
Mommy, daddy, baby, and that made you real mad?
不
No.
-认识这个吗 -人生中从来没有见过
-Recognize this? -Never seen that before in my life.
这是艾米的日记，我们在你父亲的房子里找到了这个
It's Amy's diary. We found this at your father's house.
这是你妻子的笔记吗？
Is this your wife's handwriting?
-他又不是书法鉴定... -看着是她的
-He's not a handwriting ex-- -looks like it.
我们的专家也这么觉得
Our experts thought so, too.
你想玩一点“真或假”游戏吗？
Do you wanna play a little true or false?
没问题
Sure.
“然后他擦去我唇上的糖粉，这样就可以品尝我了”
"And then he brushes the sugar off my lips so he can taste me."
是的 真的
Yeah, that's true.
你认为奎奴亚藜是一种鱼吗？
You thought quinoa was a fish?
那也是真的
That is also true, yes.
她想怀孕，你却打了他
She wanted to get pregnant, you assaulted her.
我打了她？ 不 从来没有
I hit her? No, never happened.
-这里用的“推” -完全没有
-"Pushed," it says "pushed."-Absolutely not.
我从没动过她
I never touched her.
她试图买一把枪
She tried to buy a gun.
我表示怀疑 不过我也不知道
I doubt that, but I don't know.
要我读一下最后一篇吗？
Shall I read the last entry?
当然
Sure.
“这个男人可能会杀了我”
"This man may kill me."
她自己说的“这个男人可能会杀了我”
In her own words, "this man may kill me."
一种简单的尾注罢了
It's kind of a convenient end note.
为了以后参考
For future reference...
事实是，你不是笔迹专家
The truth, you are not a handwriting expert.
好吧 我知道了
Okay, I know.
朱迪失踪的手把
Judy's missing handle.
想个2乘4的木棒，是吗？跟木棒一样大
Big as a two-by-four, right? Big as a club.
我们第一天就发现了这个，在你房子的炉火那里
We found this day one, in the fireplace in your home office.
我们不知道那他妈是什么，可是7月生炉火？
We didn't know what the hell it was, but fire in July?
我们留下了这个
We bagged it.
那个我也从来没有见过
I've never seen that before either.
我们做了测试，火没有抹灭血迹，尼克
We just tested it. Fire doesn't erase blood, Nick.
那么，最后，尼可拉斯道恩
So, finally, Nicholas dunne...
你因为谋杀你你妻子被捕了
You're under arrest for the murder of your wife.
什么都别说
Do not say another word.
-我的辩词呢  -尼克！
-What about my side? -Nick!
还要咖啡吗？
More coffee?
当然
I'd love it.
记得我们翘课开车去海角吗？
Remember that time we skipped school and drove to the cape?
老天，当然，刚从海里捉的龙虾
God, yeah. Lobster right from the ocean.
这让我想起来了
This reminds me of that.
永不结束的假期
Never-ending holiday.
你不无聊吗？
You're not bored?
德西，我怎么会无聊呢？
Desi, how could I be bored?
你可以聊聊18世纪的交响乐
You can discuss 18th-century symphonies...
19世纪印象派画家，用法语引用普鲁斯特
19th-century impressionists, quote proust in French.
尼克对文化的概念就只有电视真人秀
Nick's idea of culture was a reality TV marathon...
一只手还在他内裤里
With one hand down his boxers.
我真的得走了
I really have to get going.
不过我会尽快回来的
But I will be back just as soon as I can.
我的钥匙
My keys.
谢谢
Thank you.
男孩应该这样穿
That's how the kids wear it.
道恩？你的死律师来了
Dunne? You got one hell of a lawyer.
嘿
Hey.
-你还好吗  -嗯 你呢
-Are you okay? -Yes. Are you?
还好
Yeah.
我们走吧
Let's go.
现在什么情况
What does this mean?
你被取保候审了
Well, you're out on bond.
在我们为开庭准备的时候你可以在家休息
You can relax at home while we prep for trial.
低下头
Keep your head down.
坦纳，有艾米该死的线索吗？
Tanner, is there any fucking lead on Amy?
我已经派我最好的两个伙计去了
I've got two of my best guys on it.
她无影无踪
She's air.
回家吧，艾米，你敢吗
Come home, Amy. I dare you.
科林斯先生回来了
Mr. collings is home.
你好，科林斯先生
Hello, Mr. collings.
我想你了
I've missed you.
我一直在想
I've been thinking...
我不想失去你
I don't wanna be without you.
和我在一起
Stay with me.
等这一切都结束后，我们去希腊吧，就像你说的一样
And when all this dies down, we'll go to Greece, like you said.
吃章鱼玩拼字游戏？
Octopus and scrabble?
你认为还有多久能结束？
How long do you think until it's done?
不久了，开庭6个月，判决会很快
Not long. Six months for the trial. Sentencing will be quick.
他会上诉的
He'll appeal.
我可以在海外把剩下的戏看完
I can watch the rest overseas.
慢一点
Go slowly.
但是我想要
But I want it.
别心急
Don't rush.
做就是了（NIKE躺枪）
Just do it.
再猛烈一点
Harder.
你这个该死的贱人
You fucking bitch.
不用担心，你会有很多孩子的
Don't you worry, you're gonna have lots of babies.
她的伤符合强奸，并且还有精液
Her wounds are consistent with rape. There was semen present.
我们确定是匹配的
We'll make sure it's a match.
没错，是匹配的
Yeah, it'll match.
十分感谢你
Thank you very much.
你怎么看？
What do you think?
我们又成朋友了吗
Are we pals again?
现在我知道你没有杀你妻子，所以，是的
Now that I know you didn't murder your wife, yes.
你怎么看？
What do you think?
绑架？这故事太荒唐了
Kidnapping? The story's insane.
我们给他上了很强烈的止疼药
She's on fairly heavy painkillers.
没事，我想提供帮助
It's okay. I want to help.
道恩女士，我知道你经历了
Ms. dunne, I know what you've been through...
所以我们会尽量简短的
So we'll keep this very brief.
你能告诉我们事情的经过吗？
Can you walk us through what happened?
那天早上，门铃响了
That morning, the doorbell rang.
很平常
So normal.
我打开门
I opened the door.
太奇怪了
So strange.
从高中开始他总是甩都甩不掉
Since high school, he won't ever go away.
我只是想尽量友善一点
And I've just tried to be nice to him.
回复他的情书
Answer his letters.
让他保持冷静
Keep him calm.
噢，我的天啊
Oh, my God.
我是鼓励了他
I've encouraged him.
你不能责备你自己
You can't blame yourself.
他推门而入
He pushed inside.
他一把抓住我
And he grabbed me.
但我逃开了，并逃到了厨房
But I got away, and ran to the kitchen.
他用棍子打了我
And he clubbed me.
我倒在地上
I collapsed.
那个棍子实际上庞琦和朱迪木偶上的手把
That club was actually the handle to a punch and Judy puppet.
没错
Right.
寻宝游戏
Treasure hunt.
我把木偶藏在了格的
I'd hidden some puppets at go's--
那么德西是怎么得到那个手把的
then how did desi have that handle?
我才发现
I'd just found it.
那一定睡脱落了
It must have fallen off.
德西进来是我手上正拿着它，所以，他是从我这里拿到了手把
I was holding it when desi pushed in. So, he got it from me.
关于那个柴房
About that woodshed...
他把我带到了湖边的房子
He took me to his lake house.
把我绑到他的床上
Tied me to his bed.
很快的回到了柴房，很快
Back to the woodshed real quick. Real quick.
你去哪里放木偶时
When you went to place the puppets there...
有没有注意到那里堆了
Did you notice that it was packed--
很多东西
lots of stuff.
与你丈夫用信用卡买的东西一致
Corresponding to purchases made on credit cards in your husband's name.
尼克和信用卡
Nick and credit cards.
他老是买，我唠叨过，我不知道，可能吧
He buys, I nag. I don't know, probably.
他把很多东西藏在格那里，他们很亲近
He hid a lot of stuff at go's. They're very close.
现在我可以接着讲我被囚禁的地方了吗
Now, may I go back to where I was being held prisoner...
被一个有精神病史的人？
By a man with a history of mental problems?
请继续，道恩夫人
Please continue, Ms. dunne.
德西那晚侵犯了我
Desi assaulted me that night.
每天晚上
Every night.
他都像狗一样把我绑起来
He tied me up like a dog.
之后，就打我
And then, he'd punish me.
饿我
Starve me.
剃我毛
Shave me.
鸡奸我
Sodomize me.
那里到处都是摄像头
There were cameras everywhere.
请一定要找到，找到那些录像带
Please find this. Please find the tapes.
她用一把美工刀割开了他的喉咙
She slit his throat with a box cutter.
如果她一直被他绑着的话
How did she manageto get a hold of a box cutter...
从哪里弄来的美工刀
If he had her tied up the whole time?
你妻子回来你就不能高兴点吗？
Can't you just be happy your wife is home and safe?
艾米，我们找到你的日记了
Amy, we found your diary.
里面有很多精神和肉体虐待的描述
It contains many concerning allegations of mental and physical abuse.
没错，那是真的
Well, it's the ugly truth.
尼克不想要小孩
Nick didn't want a baby.
他经常发火，我们有经济问题
He has a temper. We had money problems.
不过我爱他
But I love him.
那你为什么想要买把枪？
Then why did you try to buy a gun?
对不起，我就我要晕过去了
I'm sorry, I feel myself fading.
我能不能澄清一件事
If I could just clarify one thing--
如果这个案子落在你们这些无能的人的身上
if this case had been left in your deeply incompetent hands...
我的丈夫就会上死刑长
My husband would be on death row...
我就会被绑的紧紧的，四肢大开
And I'd be tied, still, spread-eagle...
道恩夫人，你已经很勇敢了，我明年结束了
Ms. dunne, you've been very brave. We're finished.
现在，我要问你
Now, I have to ask you...
你觉得和你丈夫回家安全吗？
Do you feel safe going home with your husband?
感谢上帝，上帝也回应了我们的祈祷
We prayed to God, and God has answered our prayers.
艾米道恩回家了
Amy dunne is home.
现在，我知道有很多担心和疑虑
Now, I know there are a lot of questions and concerns...
不过此时此刻，我们想端坐
But for right now, we wanna sit tight...
并且感谢这密西西比河上的奇迹
And just be thankful and grateful for this miracle on the Mississippi.
抱歉 包含下 各位
Excuse me. Excuse us, folks.
我们爱你，艾米
We love you, Amy!
好了 你别再装了
All right, you can stop pretending now.
我没有装
I'm not pretending.
我在电视上看到的那个尼克就是我爱的尼克
The Nick I saw on TV, that's the Nick I fell in love with.
你知道我那些好话是专门讲给你听的吧 对吗
You do know I was just telling you what you wanted to hear, right?
你看你多了解我
That's how well you know me.
你对我的了解深入骨髓
You know me in your marrow.
好吧
Okay.
我要你把一切都坦诚交代
You need to tell me exactly what happened.
把衣服脱了
Take off your clothes.
确保你没有带窃听器
I need to make sure you're not wearing a wire.
你杀了人 艾米 你是个谋杀者
You killed someone, Amy. You're a murderer.
我是个斗士
I'm a fighter.
我披荆斩棘回到你身边
I fought my way back to you.
你杀了人
You killed a guy.
你拿美工刀割了他的喉咙
You slashed his throat with a box cutter.
你到国家电视台去，祈求我救救你
You went on national television and begged for me to save your life.
我来了
And I obliged.
不过我想要那个尼克
But I want that Nick.
我要离开你
I'm leaving.
你觉得那样明智吗？
You really think that's smart?
沐浴露
Shampoo.
受伤，被强奸的妻子拼死回到她丈夫身边
Wounded, raped wife battles her way back to her husband...
他却抛弃了她
And he deserts her.
他们会杀你的
They'll destroy you.
邻里会避开你
Neighbors will shun you.
并且我相信没人忘记你给我带来的痛苦
And I'll make sure that no one forgets the pain you caused me.
我不想跟你门外的粉丝有任何瓜葛
I don't want anything to do with your groupies outside.
他们一走
Once they go...
我就走
I go.
留一晚，睡一觉好好想想
Give it the night. Sleep on it.
真的有过孩子吗？
Was there ever a baby?
有可能
There can be.
晚安
Good night.
黑，尼克
Hey, Nick!
你好，帅哥
Hello, handsome.
可丽饼？
Crepe?
好啊
Sure.
她是他梦想中的女孩
She was his dream girl.
当这个被惯坏的富家子弟无法得到她时
And when this spoiled, rich, entitled little boy couldn't have her...
他绑架了她
He took her.
你们一定很自豪吧
You must be so proud.
已经四个小时了
It's been four hours.
尼克？尼克？你和艾米接下来怎么办？
Nick? Nick? What's next for you and Amy?
目前，我们一心一意经营我们的婚姻
Right now, it's all about our marriage.
当两人相爱但有无法实现
When two people love each other and can't make that work...
那才是真正的悲剧
That's the real tragedy.
亲吻我的脸颊
Kiss my cheek.
我不敢相信这他妈的骗子竟然成了美国甜心
I can't believe that fucking spider is America's sweetheart.
她亲口告诉我她杀了德西
She told me she killed desi.
不是自卫，是谋杀
Not self-defense. Murder.
我们就不能弄个窃听器吗？ -那没用
-Can't we get a wire? -That's not gonna work.
她之前给你说过一次
She told you once before.
是啊 那是因为我当时一丝不挂 站在浴室里
Yeah, because she had me strip naked, and stand in the shower.
我发誓你们是我见过最有病的人
I swear, you two are the most fucked-up people I've ever known.
而我专门研究有病的人
And I specialize in fucked-up.
你和艾米还住在一起？
You and Amy under the same roof?
你们真应该报名真人秀
You should pitch that as reality television.
艾米道恩和密西西比河上的奇迹
Amy dunne, and the miracle on the Mississippi.
我和尼克经历了艰难困苦
Nick and I have been through some bad patches.
经历了黑暗大的时日
We've had our dark days.
但我们非常感谢你们
But we thank you so much...
感谢你们对我们新生活的支持，感谢你们原谅尼克
For supporting us in our new life together, for forgiving Nick.
真的，你们的鼓励就是我的全部
Really, your encouragement means the world.
她真是棒极了
She's good.
超凡艾米和谦卑的丈夫
Amazing Amy and the humbled husband.
布兰森家庭主妇真人秀
The real housewives of branson.
照顾好这个家伙，好吗？
Take care of this guy, will you?
不敢相信你就这样撇下我不管了
I can't believe you're just leaving now.
你不再有危险了
You are not at risk anymore.
我的处境就是“危险”的最佳定义
I'm the definition of "at risk."
你有一本书要出，一部电影，还可以开连锁“酒吧”
You got a book deal, a lifetime movie, you franchised the bar.
你要谢谢她
You may wanna thank her.
只是不要把她惹毛了
Just don't piss her off.
再见，伙计
See you, guys.
埃尔维斯离开密苏里州了
Elvis has left Missouri.
她一定有过什么疏忽
She had to have made a mistake.
我们要一页一页地核查艾米的故事
We need to check Amy's story, piece by piece.
尼克，我什么都做不了
Nick, I can't do anything.
我们吸引了全国的目光，我们什么都没查出来
We had the national spotlight on us, we stained the rug.
这案子现在是联邦政府的了，他们已经结案了
The case is with the feds now, they're done.
那并不代表你不能继续调查了啊
That doesn't mean you have to be done.
结了
It does.
你在做什么
What are you doing?
睡不着
Couldn't sleep.
过来
Come on...
我带你上床
Let me tuck you back in.
你知道你能和我一起睡，是吗？
You know you can sleep with me, right?
是的 只是...
Yeah, it's just...
我还需要点时间
I need more time.
我再也不会伤害你了
I would never, ever hurt you.
我真的需要你的配合
I do need you to participate, though.
我需要你做好你的本分
I need you to do your part.
好吧
Okay.
你听说的有关我妻子的一切
Everything you have heard about my wife...
都是弥天大谎
Is a lie.
她是一个工于心计、蓄意杀人的变态
She is a calculating, murderous psychopath.
对此我也有责任
And I have been complicit--
尼克？吃早餐了
Nick? Breakfast.
亲爱的
Honey?
我们应该握着手
We should hold hands.
没必要随时，但要是不是的
Not the entire time, but on and off throughout.
“哪儿，尼克，你妻子回来了你是什么感受？”
"So, Nick, how does it feel to have your wife back?"
“简直好极了
"It's fantastic.
”又有几个人能拥有第二次去爱的机会
"How many people are lucky enough to get a second chance at love?"
“棒极了”有点轻率
"Fantastic" is a little flippant.
“太神奇了？
"Amazing"?
我要你承认是你用的那些信用卡
I need you to admit that you got the credit cards...
并且把东西都藏在戈那里，而且你推搡过我
And that you hid all that stuff at go's and that you pushed me.
我需要这三样东西才能感觉安全
I'm gonna need those three things to feel safe.
你必须承认，尼克
You have to own this, Nick.
别担心 我知道该说什么
Don't worry. I know exactly what to say.
尼克
Nick.
多么漂亮的房子
What a beautiful home.
很感谢你给我这个机会，尼克
I so appreciate you giving us this time, Nick.
你上了国家电视台
You went on national television...
告诉人们我谋杀了我妻子
And told people that I murdered my wife.
我只是顺着故事而已
I go where the story goes.
你暗还示我和我姐姐发生过肉体关系
You implied that I had carnal relations with my sister.
我没有那么说，我只是说你们“极其亲密”
I didn't use the "I" word. I said you two were "extremely close."
你和一群脑残还把我定义为反社会者
You and a panel of nitwits diagnosed me as a sociopath.
我们活跃一下气氛
Ice-breaker.
和你的机器狗相配
To go with your robot dog.
我去叫艾米下来
I'll go find Amy.
她在楼下了
She's downstairs.
这是什么？ -这是给你的
-What is it? -It's for you.
打开
Open it.
我不需要你给的任何礼物
I don't need any more gifts from you.
打开
Open it.
我最近都没碰过你
I didn't touch you.
你不需要碰我
You didn't need to.
放屁 那张精液废弃通知单
Bullshit. That notice of disposal.
我收到过 你扔进了垃圾箱
I have that. You threw it out.
没错，那个通知单
The notice, yes.
我要血液测试
I want a blood test.
我要亲子鉴定
I want a paternity test.
我喜欢测试
I love tests.
你随便叫那些人怎么憎恨我都行
You can teach those people to hate me all you want.
我不在乎 我要走了
I don't care. I am leaving you.
我都不用叫你孩子讨厌你
I won't have to teach your child to hate you.
他自己就会那样做
He'll do that all by himself.
艹你妈个贱逼
You fucking cunt!
我是你娶的贱逼
I'm the cunt you married.
你唯一喜欢你自己的时候
The only time you liked yourself...
就是你师徒成为你眼前这个贱逼也许喜欢的人的时候
Was when you were trying to be someone this cunt might like.
我不会半途而废，我就是贱逼
I'm not a quitter. I'm that cunt.
我为你杀了人，谁还能这么说？
I've killed for you. Who else can say that?
你认为你和一个漂亮的中西部女孩在一起会幸福吗？
You think you would be happy with a nice midwestern girl?
没门，宝贝，是我
No way, baby. I'm it.
你有妄想症 你彻底疯了
Look, you're delusional. You're insane.
现在这样对你有好处吗
Why would you even want this?
是 我曾经爱过你
Yes, I loved you.
然后我们做的就是憎恨彼此 试图控制彼此
And then all we did was resent each other, and try to control each other.
让彼此受伤
And cause each other pain.
这就是婚姻
That's marriage.
现在我准备好了
Now, I'm getting ready.
我不忍心看着你和那玩意儿在接下来的18年玩过家家
I can't watch you play house with that thing for the next 18 years.
我不能就这样走人啊
I can't just walk away.
你可以得到孩子的监护权
You could get custody.
不 我不会的 你知道的
No, I won't. And you know it.
那是我的孩子 我不能抛弃他
It's gonna be my child. I'm not gonna leave it.
你想要留下来
You wanna stay.
这是我的责任 不是我想怎样就怎样了
I have a responsibility. It's not about what I want anymore.
你想和她在一起
You wanna stay with her.
你伤了我的心
You're breaking my heart.
格 你是我理性的声音
Go, you're my voice of reason.
我需要你和一起面对
I need you with me on this.
我当然和你在一起
Of course I'm with you.
我们出生之前就在一起了
I was with you before we were even born.
我们一同穿越黑暗
We've been through the darkness.
我们熬到了尽头 齐心协力
We've come out, united.
我们交流
We communicate.
我们对彼此推心置腹
We're honest with each other.
对吧
Right?
我们是凶案中的伙伴
We're partners in crime.
还有呢？
And?
还有？
我们就要成为父母了
We're gonna be parents.
我的天啊！
My goodness!
“你在想什么”
"What are you thinking?"
“你在感觉这什么
"How are you feeling?"
“我们对彼此做了什么
"What have we done to each other?"
“我们将去往何方？”
"What will we do?"